[Music]
[Música]
ch
ch
Oh
Oh
ah
ah
Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
and
y
a
un
[Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
Okay good
Bueno buenas
night
noches
Uh Good night good night [ __ ] man
Eh Buenas noches buenas noches [__] tío
no it wasn't going to be
no no iba a ser
direct I'm dead man I come from
directo estoy muerto tío vengo de
badajos I've been with with a friend
badajos que he estado con con un colega
with Alex no nosop Well I'll tag him
con Alex no nosop Bueno ya lo etiquetaré
on Instagram who did a
en instagram que me ha hecho una sesión
really cool photo shoot as soon as I have it
de fotos guapísima en cuanto la tenga
because we'll upload it but I got myself into a
pues la iremos subiendo pero me metí una
beating man because in the end eh It's 2
paliza tío porque al final eh Son 2
hours and quar 2 hours and quar 2 hours and a
horas y cuar 2 horas y cuar 2 horas y
half I thought it was
media me creía que era
less
menos
a kiss a kiss
un beso un beso
rami that nothing man I got a big kiss I got
rami que nada tío que me he pegado una
up early and I was tired and I
pizota he madrugado y estaba cansado y
say just like that and as soon as I got home as soon as I
digo tal y como tal y como llegue a casa
got home I was going to go
tal y como llegue a casa me iba a ir
to bed but I took a shower and I have
para la cama pero me he duchado y tengo
a few things to comment on and I'm
unas cuantas de cositas que comentaros y
going to comment on them and I'm not going to be here for
las voy a comentar y no voy a estar
long but I'm going to comment on them okay
mucho tiempo pero voy a comentarlas vale
Open telesalseo Javi come on Laura
Abre telesalseo Javi venga Laura ahora
right now let's cut the salsería and go
mismo cortamos la salsería y nos vamos
to telesalseo Laura Please yes
para telesalseo Laura Por favor si
we are opening
estamos abriendo
[ __ ] Let's see let's see it step by step I won't
[__] A ver vamos a ver por partes no
go on too much look there is Alex it was
me enrollo mucho mira ahí está el Alex
worth it going into the woods
ha valido la pena meterse en el bosque
Well yes it was worth it I
Bueno sí ha valido la pena que me he
came back with a sheet full of [ __ ] and
venido con una sábana llena de [__] y
some boots also full of [ __ ]
unos botines también llena de [__]
but well but literal [ __ ] eh I mean
pero bueno pero [__] literal eh o sea
not dirty but [ __ ] okay he put me
no sucio sino [__] vale me ha metido
in a woods and all that eh
en un bosque y tal
Well I'll show you the picture
eh Bueno ya os enseñaré la fotillo por
Alex is over there I'll show you the picture
ahí está Alex ya os enseñaré la fotillo
But well within what there is within
Pero bueno dentro de lo que hay dentro
what there is the best that
de lo que hay se ha hecho lo mejor que
could be seen let's see a few
se puede A ver vamos a ver unas cuantas
things no I didn't see the fights on
de cosas no no vi los combates en el
Jordi's Channel I don't like that
Canal de de Jordi no me gustan esas
stuff I mean I don't know if they're showing any gossip
cosas o sea no sé que pasen algún salseo
or anything like that I don't know if there will be
o algo por el estilo que no sé si habrá
any for the news
alguno para el noticiero
tomorrow
mañana
no I don't know if I'll see any  gossip that I don't know
no a no s que vea algún salseo que no sé
if there has been anything eh with the issue
si habrá habido algo eh con el tema
of the guy and
de del tiparraco y
all that. I think I saw on
demás Creo que vi en
Twitter someone say that they threw
Twitter a alguien decir que le tiraron
a lot at
mucho a
Comanche, I think David Suárez made
Comanche creo que el David Suárez hizo
a lot of jokes about
muchos chistes de
Comanche, right? Karime, right? Karime exactly? Right?
Comanche verdad Karime verdad Karime tal
Karime exactly? Let's
cual verdad Karime tal
see in parts Okay and it just
cual a ver por partes Vale y acaba de
happened a little while ago it just happened
ocurrir hace un rato acaba de ocurrir
a little while ago okay in the last live
hace un rato vale en el último directo
that I did I gave you an exclusive that to me
que hice os di una exclusiva que a mí me
seemed like a bomb exclusive okay it
parecía una exclusiva bomba vale me
seemed like an
parecía una
exclusive man, not as bomb as the one in
exclusiva hombre no tan bomba como la de
the afternoon, but well, quite big, quite
por la tarde pero bueno bastante gorda
big for many colors I don't know
bastante gorda para muchos colores no sé
which of the two It would be more more powerful
cuál de las dos Sería más más potente
okay but I was commenting on an
vale pero os estuve comentando una
exclusive that had been leaked to me
exclusiva que me habían filtrado
and well, things have happened okay
y Y bueno pues han pasado cositas vale
eh I was commenting on an exclusive that had been
eh estuve comentando una exclusiva que
leaked to me in fact Well, the
me habían filtrado de hecho Bueno los
media, various media, not only
medios varios medios no solamente
Movistar but various media have
Movistar sino que varios medios han
echoed the exclusive that
hecho eco de la de la exclusiva que
we gave okay uh basically Rubius and
dimos vale eh básicamente pues Rubius y
Gref are involved in a new
gref están metidos en un nuevo
project, I don't know what role they play, I
proyecto no sé qué papel juegan eso lo
made that clear okay I always tell you as far as I
dejé claro vale Yo siempre os digo hasta
know okay, that is, when  I can say or
donde sé vale o sea cuando puedo decir o
Hey, well this is how it is, I'm telling you as far
Oye pues esto es así os lo digo hasta
as I know, okay, I mean, if I knew that
donde sé vale o sea si si supiera que
this project was directly theirs, I would have
este proyecto es directamente de ellos
told you it was theirs, they both
os hubiera dicho es de ellos ellos dos
are the owners of the company. But I don't
son los dueños de la empresa Pero no lo
know, I know that they are involved and that they
sé sé que ellos están involucrados y que
are involved in some way, okay, I think I
están metidos de alguna forma vale creo
think in fact that they are the
Creo de hecho que son la imagen
main image of this new platform. Okay,
principal de esta nueva plataforma Vale
but I don't know if the platform is theirs,
pero no sé si la plataforma es de ellos
like when Dallas did
dos como en plan cuando Dallas hizo
tardeos
tardeos
or or that they are being
o o que ellos pues están siendo
hired to make the face, the image
contratados para hacer la cara la imagen
of this new platform, okay, I told you
de esta nueva plataforma vale os dije
the colors, I told you the colors, I told you the name, okay, I told you the colors, I told you
los colores os dije los colores os dije
the name, do you remember well? Well,
dije el nombre os acordáis bien pues
after our
después de nuestra
news, after our news,
noticia después de nuestra noticia
okay,
vale
dedo.com has published its
dedo.com ha publicado su
page,
página
okay, I imagine
vale me imagino
that I
que
imagine it was because
me imagino que habrá sido porque
we said so because it's that it's that it's that it's that it's not that it's not that no and yes, it's green, no no
nosotros lo hemos dicho porque es que es
no it's the name, it's green and it's a
no no no es el nombre es verde y es una
streamer platform, okay, I
plataforma de streamer vale o
mean, let's see, I had it, the things that I said, I
sea a ver lo tenía el las cosas que dije
had them very
las tenía muy
tied up, okay, the things
atadas vale las cosas
that Karime send it to me, send it to me and  I see it
que Karime mándamelo mándamelo y lo veo
okay I haven't been there for a long time Oh my
vale que no vo hasa mucho tiempo Oh my
God no no let's see the thing that I told you I
God no no a ver la cosa que os dije
had very tied up what I don't know okay I think Let's
tenía muy atada lo que no sé vale Yo yo
see I'm going to tell you the
pienso A ver os voy a decir la
truth I think that Gref and
verdad yo pienso que gref y
Rubius have a lot to do with the
Rubius tienen mucho que ver en la
platform in the sense that maybe they have
plataforma en el sentido a lo mejor han
put pass I don't know okay
puesto pasa No lo sé vale
But let's see at least at least they
Pero a ver como mínimo como mínimo pues
are the image I mean they are the two that are going to
son la imagen o sea son los dos que van
sponsor
a patrocinar
This is
Esto
worth it at least and nothing well look at you that
vale como mínimo y nada pues fíjate tú
we leaked the news before last
que filtramos la noticia antes de ayer
night Just like uh the name that I told you
noche Tal cual eh el nombre que os dije
uh streaming platform Okay and the
eh plataforma de streaming Vale y el
color like I told you just like uh I mean
color como os lo dije tal cual eh o sea
this web page was not published the
esta página web no estaba publicada el
other
otro
day this web page was not there the other
día esta página web no estaba el otro
day okay it was this afternoon When did it come
día vale ha sido esta tarde de Cuándo ha
out
salido
Uh I've received other things but I can't
Eh me han llegado otras cosas pero no os
tell you because it's
la puedo contar porque
not safe for me to
no no es seguro para mí
tell it it's not safe for me to tell it
contarlo no es seguro para mí contarlo
okay I can't tell you yet okay
vale no os lo puedo contar todavía vale
but other things have arrived No
pero me han llegado otras cosas No
man joke it's that I don't have it tied up
hombre coña es que no lo tengo atado
okay But well More or less more or less it
vale Pero bueno Más o menos más o menos
goes like that there it goes
por ahí va por ahí van los tiros
HM shots to Let's see, it's a company
HM a A ver es una empresa la que está
behind this, I've been investigating a
detrás de esta he estado investigando un
little. Okay, and the people behind
poco Vale y la gente que está detrás de
the people behind this
la gente que está detrás de esta
platform,
plataforma
okay, it's a Spanish streaming platform,
vale es una plataforma de streaming
okay, so it inaugurated it and
española vale o sea la la inaugura y la
created it, and the investment, especially the
ha creado y la inversión sobre todo la
investment, is made by Spanish people,
inversión la hace gente española
eh, I don't know if Rubius and Greev have
eh yo no sé si Rubius y greev tienen
anything to do with it, some of them are
algo que ver a nivel son algunos son
owners, they are shareholders. I don't know, okay, I
dueños son accionistas No lo sé vale
think that surely, I don't think that they
creo que seguramente no creo que
are probably, well, simply
seguramente sean pues simplemente que
like when Mixer hired Greev or
como cuando mixer contrató a greev o
this type of thing, not like when Ki
este tipo de cosas no como cuando ki se
took Weol, I think it's like that, okay,
ha llevado a weol creo que es así vale
in all honesty, because I've been
en honor a la verdad porque he estado
looking to see, I've been looking a little
mirando a ver He estado mirando un poco
at Who Who is behind
sobre Quiénes Quiénes están detrás de
This, okay, and they are very powerful people, they
Esto vale Y son personas muy potentes
are people, eh, they are well-known in the
son personas eh son conocidas en el
business world, I'm not going to tell you their
mundo de los negocios no os voy a decir
names because it's not necessary
nombre Porque tampoco es necesario
because, well, let's see, it's public. I mean, if
porque bueno a ver es público O sea si
you know how to search for it, you will find it, but
sabéis buscarlo lo Vais a encontrar pero
if I tell you the names here, you will not
si os digo Aquí los nombres No vais a
know who they are, okay, eh, but they are
saber quiénes son vale eh pero son
very important people in the
personas muy importante en el en el
world of business and
mundo de los negocios y de las
telecommunications they just show their faces just let's
telecomunicaciones solo ponen la cara
see just show their faces it's not just
nada más a ver solo poner la cara nada
any nonsense I mean it's not
más no es cualquier tontería O sea no es
like Okay yeah here I'll lend you my photo
como Bueno sí toma te presto mi foto
so you can put it there No man no let's
para que la pongas ahí No hombre no a
see there's a big contract behind it And
ver ahí hay un contrato gordo detrás Y
that will surely imply that they
eso implicará seguramente que ellos
will have to do streaming on this
tendrán que hacer streaming en esta
platform you understand So it's not
plataforma me entiendes Entonces no es
like Okay just no no let's see berito
como Bueno solamente no no a ver berito
a kiss okay eh There are people the people
un beso vale eh Hay gente la gente que
behind this project okay the
está detrás de este proyecto vale la
people behind this project
gente que está detrás de este proyecto
are very powerful people eh Very reliable eh And
es gente muy potente eh Muy fiable eh Y
with very good business eh And with very
con muy buenos negocios eh Y con muy
good business I mean the truth is that I've
buenos negocios O sea la verdad es que
been taking a look and they are
estado echando un vistazo y son gente
very
muy
important people in the business world
importante en el mundo de los negocios
okay Spanish they are very powerful people very
vale españoles son gente muy potente muy
powerful and in the world of
poderosa y en el mundo de las
telecommunications Okay then
telecomunicaciones Vale entonces pues
we'll see what they surprise us with
veremos a ver con qué nos sorprenden
but here there is here let's see they are going to
pero aquí hay aquí hay a ver se va a
try to have a future
intentar que haya futuro
eh it's
eh
going to come Stepping
va a venir Pisando
strong What yes I ask you all okay let's
fuerte Lo que sí Os pido a todos vale
defend ourselves
que defendámonos
first
primero
Okay and you have found out first those of you
Vale y os habéis enterado primero los
who are subscribed here no no it's not Piqué it's not Piqué Let's
que estáis aquí suscritos no no es Piqué
see it's not  no one famous let's
no es Piqué A ver no es nadie famoso a
see if they're famous if they're famous people the
ver si es famoso si son gente famosa la
people behind this at
gente que está detrás de esto por lo
least in the face of the company okay they're
menos de Cara a la empresa vale son
famous people in the business world
gente famosa en el mundo de los negocios
but if I tell you Here the names are
pero si yo os digo Aquí los nombres os
going to sound the same as if I tell you
va a sonar a lo mismo que si os digo
Fernando Rodriguez I mean no they're not
Fernando Rodríguez O sea no no son gente
well-known people eh in the world of streaming nor let's
conocida eh en el mundo del streaming ni
see they're big businessmen they're
a ver son empresarios gordos son
big businessmen s said it before no
empresarios gordos s lo dijo antes no
my life no
vida mía no
impossible impossible Javi you're going to get into
imposible imposible Javi te vas a meter
that Well I don't know look they've released they've
en eso Pues no lo sé mira han sacado han
released this page Okay and they've left
sacado esta página Vale y han dejado
here like the email so that people
aquí como el email para que la gente
Launch the request okay leave us your email
Lance la solicitud vale déjanos tu email
and s one of the first ders the name
y s uno de los primeros ders el nombre
seems a little strange to me right now I don't know
me parece un poco raro ahora mismo no sé
if we'll end up getting used to it But well
si terminaremos acostumbrando Pero bueno
for now There it is for
de momento Ahí
now There it is
está de momento Ahí está
okay There you have it exclusive confirmed
vale Ahí lo tenéis exclusiva confirmada
exclusive confirmed okay do we do okay we'll
exclusiva confirmada vale do we do vale
see let's see eh it's still to be known H
ya veremos a ver eh falta por saber H
well it's still to be known well name
pues falta por saber bueno nombre
confirmed color confirmed
confirmado color confirmado plataforma
streaming platform and at the moment that we
de streaming y en el momento que hemos
leaked the information here at the
filtrado la información aquí en la
salsería okay
salsería vale
eh what they did this afternoon they were
eh lo que han hecho esta tarde han sido
publish eh the website okay but they have
publicar eh la página web vale pero han
published the website but they have not
publicado la página web pero no han
made any announcement on social
hecho ningún anuncio en
media they have not made they have not made any
redes no han hecho no han hecho ningún
announcement on social media I mean we
anuncio en redes o sea lo hemos
found it this afternoon by chance I don't
encontrado esta tarde de casualidad no
know what we were looking for But well
sé que estábamos buscando Pero bueno
something else let's see This is in 20 minutes But
cosa a ver Esto es en 20 minutos Pero
well the media has also echoed
bueno se han hecho eco los medios
this news Auron Play and Villin
de esta noticia auron Play y villin
would have broken up according to the
habrían roto según el creador de
content creator Javi Oliveira okay they have
contenido Javi oliveira vale se han
echoed it in several media outlets
hecho eco en varios medios de
and I think it's great because
comunicación y me parece Genial porque
also [ __ ] the truth is that it is
además [__] la verdad es que se
quite appreciated when credits are given
agradece bastante cuando se dan créditos
okay it is an exclusive Look I'm going to
vale es una es una exclusiva Mira os voy
tell you something true because there are a
a decir una cosa de verdad porque hay
lot of people trying to discredit This
mucha gente intentando desacreditar Esto
okay what I have said is what I have
vale lo que yo he dicho es lo que yo he
said okay there are many occasions in which
dicho vale hay muchas ocasiones en las
I uh have
que yo
given an exclusive and then
eh he dado una exclusiva y luego me
people come to me and say Oh but
viene la gente y me dice Ay pero es que
you said that this was with h and then it is
tú dijiste que esto era con h y luego se
written without h I mean no don't come to me with
escribe sin h o sea no no me vengáis con
nonsense okay don't tell me don't come to me
tonterías vale no me digáis no me
with more nonsense okay I mean
vengáis con más tonterías vale o sea
everyone knows uh the appreciation that I
todo el mundo sabe eh el aprecio que yo
have for Eh  Well, for these two
tengo por Eh bueno por estos dos
content creators, as for
creadores de contenido al igual que por
many others, no, but [ __ ], they're people who
otros muchos no pero [__] son gente que
have always treated me very well,
a mí siempre me han tratado muy bien
obviously. These are news that I have to
evidentemente Son noticias que yo tengo
give. I know that they understand
que dar sé que ellos lo entienden
perfectly. They may feel better or
perfectamente les pueden sentar mejor o
worse that I have to give this type of
peor que yo tenga que dar este tipo de
news. But if I have the exclusive, eh,
noticias pero si tengo la exclusiva eh
if I have the exclusive tied up, I'm going to give it,
si tengo la exclusiva atada la voy a dar
okay. And obviously, I think you have to
vale Y evidentemente yo creo que hay que
be stupid, okay, eh, but I'm not saying this for
ser lelo vale eh pero no lo digo por
any creator because I don't think any
ningún creador porque creo que ningún
creator has questioned me or anything like that,
creador me ha puesto en duda ni nada por
okay, but yes, people on Twitter,
el estilo vale pero sí gente de Twitter
Twitter accounts, no, let's see. You have to
cuentas de Twitter no a ver hay Hay que
be stupid to think that I'm going to get
ser lelo para para pensar que yo me voy
burned by news
a quemar con una noticia
like that. I'm not going to get burned by something like that.
así no me voy a quemar con una cosa así
If I'm telling you that it's confirmed, it's
Si te estoy diciendo que está confirmado
confirmed. I mean, don't give it
es que está confirmado O sea no le deis
another thought. I know that there are many accounts
más vueltas yo sé que hay muchas cuentas
on Twitter that are superfans of the couple,
en Twitter que son superfan de la pareja
eh, as a couple, okay. And they want to cling
eh como pareja vale Y quieren aferrarse
to something that isn't reality, okay,
a una cosa que no es la realidad vale
yes, Auron said that he has a
que sí que auron ha dicho que tiene una
sweatshirt, which is very good. That's perfect. What
sudadera que muy bien Que perfecto que
I'm telling you is that they're not together,
yo te estoy diciendo que no están juntos
I'm telling you. I don't follow them day to
yo te estoy diciendo Yo no sigo el día a
day.  of them okay I don't follow the day to day
día de ellos vale No sigo el día a día
of what they have been saying in the Stream
de lo que han ido diciendo en el Stream
but apparently Well yes they have been
pero por lo visto Pues sí han ido
pretending, let's see, they have a friendship and I
fingiendo a ver tienen una amistad y
think that they will have affection for each other for
creo que cariño se van a tener toda la
life obviously unless
vida evidentemente a no ser que pase
something bad happens which I think will not be the
algo feo que creo que no va a ser el
case and hopefully it's not worth it because I think they
caso y ojalá que no vale pues yo creo
will mention each other with affection
que se van a mencionar con cariño
for life okay I don't know if they are
durante toda la vida vale Yo no sé si se
going to if they are going to speak out I think it's
van a si se van a pronunciar ellos creo
not worth it from what I understand
que no vale por lo que tengo entendido
No man, let's see, there will come a time in
No hombre a ver llegará un momento en
the next few weeks when maybe they wo
las próximas semanas en las que a lo
n't be a live show together
mejor no van a ser un directo juntos
like the other time but there will come a time
como la otra vez pero llegará un momento
in some live show or something that
en algún en algún directo o algo que
will say Hey, look, it's true that
dirá Oye pues mira que es verdad que no
we are not okay, I mean, they will
estamos vale o sea lo van a decir
surely say it Not for nothing but because they are not going to be
seguramente No por nada sino porque no
deceiving people in an
van a estar engañando a la gente de
it way you know yes it's true that they don't have to
forma it sabes sí que es verdad que no
give explanations about their
tienen por qué dar explicaciones de su
private lives but no, they don't live together anymore
vida privada pero no no viven juntos ya
for real I mean, I know that there are many
de verdad O sea sé que hay muchas
Twitter accounts and Felix a kiss I know
cuentas de Twitter e Félix un beso sé
that there are many Twitter accounts
que hay muchas cuentas de Twitter
stubborn in clinging to something that is
emperradas en aferrarse a una cosa que
not  real okay I mean I'm
no es real vale o sea os lo estoy
telling you I'm not going to get burned with this
diciendo no me voy a quemar con esta
information for God's sake we're not talking about
información por Dios no estamos hablando
if this platform had been
de si la plataforma esta hubiera sido
blue Imagine if I had made a mistake
azul Imagínate que me hubiese equivocado
with the color and the name okay well okay but
en el color y el nombre vale bueno Vale
more or less I was on track But it's that
pero más o menos encaminado iba Pero es
in this no it's not that I'm not on
que en esto no no es que no vaya
track or I'm not on track It's that I
encaminado o no vaya encaminado Es que
'm confirming the news soul a
te estoy confirmando la noticia alma un
kiss okay I'm confirming the
beso vale Te estoy confirmando la
news okay I confirmed it in the morning and I
noticia vale la confirmé por la mañana y
confirmed it in the afternoon without
la re que te confirmé por la tarde sin
further ado there's no more turns it's not that Auron
más no hay más vueltas no es que auron
mentioned a sweatshirt it's not that Auron
ha mencionado sudadera no es que auron
mentioned a documentary it's that
ha mencionado un documental es que que
no that I don't care that eh they said
no que me da igual que eh ellos dijeron
like they had leaks and I know about
como que tenían goteras y se
Setup but it hasn't changed let's see it's
de de Setup pero no se ha cambiado a ver
changed the Setup but it's changed but quite
se ha cambiado de Setup pero se ha
changed
cambiado de Setup pero bien cambiado
okay dom Javi I swear it's the first
vale dom Javi Te juro que es la primera
time I don't see to become a member it must
vez que no veo para hacerme miembro debe
be El Whisky or that I'm playing
ser El Whisky o que estoy jugando a
cyberpunk while I write to you
cyberpunk mientras te escribo
LoL a kiss it's the first time I don't see
LoL un beso es la primera vez que no veo
to be my member eh It's next to the
para ser mi miembro eh Está al lado del
subscribe button okay  eh what was said
botón de suscribirse vale eh lo dicho
okay so I mean no I'm not going to get into in in
vale o sea es que no no voy a entrar en
debates okay I'm not going to get into
en en debates vale no voy a entrar en
debates of yes yes yes no what if
debates de si sí de si no de que si
now I don't know what what if now
ahora no sé qué de que si ahora me sale
a Twitter account pops up saying let's
una cuenta de Twitter diciendo vamos a
see nobody eh I know that I know that there are people who
ver nadie eh sé que sé que hay gente que
are trying to discredit me But
está intentando desacreditarme Pero
simply because it's me okay It's not that
simplemente porque soy yo vale No es que
this information was on Twitter no
esta información estaba en Twitter no
this information was not on Twitter on
esta información no estaba en Twitter en
Twitter there were rumors and suspicions
Twitter había rumores y sospechas Por
Why Well because they had noticed that there was
qué Pues porque habían notado que aquí
something strange here eh Because they had noticed
había una rareza eh Porque habían notado
that here I don't know what okay very well but one
que aquí no sé qu vale muy bien pero una
thing is suspicions and another thing is what
cosa son las sospechas y otra cosa es lo
I'm here to tell you exclusively the day
que yo te vengo a contar en exclusiva
before yesterday what I'm here to
antes de ayer lo que yo te vengo a
tell you
contar en
exclusively okay No Francisco no Javi you
exclusiva vale No Francisco no Javi tú
made a video without informing yourself
hiciste un vídeo sin informarte
Francisco Take a walk in the park I'm
Francisco Date una vuelta por el parque
going to repeat it to you confirmed
te lo voy a volver a repetir confirmado
confirmed okay It's not that it was already
confirmadísimo vale No es que ya estaba
on Twitter no on Twitter there were
en Twitter de hace no en Twitter estaban
the rumors people saying no this no
los rumores la gente diciendo no esto no
this and multi-accounts also made up thing
esto y multicuentas tamb inventados cosa
no what I'm here to tell you is
no lo que yo te vengo a decir es
confirmed confirmed
confirmado confirmadísimo
they broke up at some point well  They are going to
han roto en algún momento pues lo van a
confirm without more it is that I am not going to enter
confirmar sin más es que no voy a entrar
to debate Sources Miami Miami to me
a debatir Fuentes Miami Miami me lo
man no Sources Miami confirmed it to me
hombre no Fuentes Miami me lo confirmó
No if you want I will put here the
No si quieres te pongo aquí las
conversations that I have had with the
conversaciones que he tenido yo con la
people that I have had to have
gente que haya tenido que tener de
really is that you believe that how do
verdad es que ustedes os creéis que cómo
you believe that things work that I
os creéis que funcionan las cosas que yo
have to reveal the sources that I
tengo que revelar las fuentes que yo os
have for you that it is
tengo que
not worth it eh I was going to see it here but I think
no vale eh iba a verlo aquí pero creo
Karime is sending it to me ah no yes Well let's see
Karime ah no sí Bueno a ver el hermano
Auron's brother has posted an
de auron ha puesto una historia de
Instagram story they have a reason to be together I
Instagram tienen por qué estar juntos
understand anyway all quite diffuse
entiendo en fin todos bastante difusos
we will see How Gavi evolves for example
veremos Cómo evoluciona gavi por ejemplo
directly confirmed the news that they are
directamente confirmó la noticia la de
no longer together I say attitude that
que ya no están juntos digo actitud que
woke up the sleeping beast brother
despertó a la bestia dormida el hermano
Dauron Play this little message dedicated to him I
dauron Play este mensajito le dedicó
have 52 hours of investigation I give you
llevo 52 horas de investigación os doy
an exclusive Give me money s days without
una exclusiva Denme dineros s días sin
sleep studying everything when in truth
dormir estudiando todo cuando en verdad
the Source is a 3 second WhatsApp message
la Fuente es un mensaje de WhatsApp de 3
I am a Secret Agent of the FBI
segundos soy Agente Secreto del FBI
well he does not deny it
bueno no lo desmiente
okay No Messi verga did not give an
vale No el Messi [__] no dio una
exclusive Messi verga commented The
exclusiva el Messi [__] comentó La
donation that  they did to Sara for
donación que le hicieron a Sara de
real really is that I got irritated and I
verdad de verdad es que me irrit y me
went to bed eh No queca they didn't give the
voy a la cama eh No queca no dieron el
name of the new girl it's
nombre de la nueva chica son
speculation you don't understand
especulaciones ustedes no entendéis
between rumors and confirm the difference you
entre rumores y confirmar la diferencia
don't
no la
know her rumors and
conocéis rumores y
confirm okay rumors and confirm
confirmar vale rumores y confirmar el
Auro's brother doesn't deny it doesn't
hermano de Auro no lo niega no lo
deny it he's telling me that Eh well
desmiente me está diciendo que Eh bueno
that I have said that I have confirmed it I do
que que yo he dicho que lo he confirmado
n't know what I don't know how much and in reality I
no sé qué no sé cuánto y en realidad
only confirmed it with a couple of
solamente lo confirmé con un par de
WhatsApp well it was exactly a
WhatsApp bueno fueron exactamente una
call in the morning another at noon and
llamada por la mañana otra al mediodía y
a few audios in the afternoon those
unos cuantos de audios por la tarde eso
were the three chats with three
fueron las tres charlas con tres
people that I had to get to
personas que tuve para llegar hasta
where I
donde yo
wanted without further ado okay
quería sin más
without
vale sin
further ado what Messi verga comments is a
más lo que Comenta Messi [__] es una
donation that yes that yes that that's what we
donación que eso sí
talked about okay or so what
que de eso sí que hablamos vale o sea lo
Messi verga comments The donation that they
que Comenta Messi [__] La donación que
make to him there okay well Messi verga and
le hacen aí vale bueno Messi [__] y
everyone okay on
todos vale en
Twitter it's a multi-account okay Because
Twitter es una multicuenta vale Porque
yes it is true that there are people
sí que es verdad que hay gente
who yes it is true that there are people who
que sí que es verdad que hay gente que
are speculating just as they have been
está especulando al igual que han estado
speculating with this breakup that I already
especulando con esta ruptura que ya os
signed it okay the breakup is confirmed and
la firmo vale la ruptura está confirmada
Well, you're going to see it in the
e Pues es que lo Vais a ver en las
next few days, it's probably
próxim en los próximos días seguramente
okay. But the fact that they're speculating
vale Pero ya el que estén especulando
about Bin having
con Bin que estuviera que estuviera
something with Ribor or that Auron
teniendo algo con ribor o que auron
had something with
estuviera teniendo algo con
Paulet, I told you here in the video, I
paulet yo aquí os dije en el vídeo yo
told you here in the video that they're denying
aquí os dije en el vídeo que a
it to me,
mí me lo
okay, they're
desmienten vale
denying it to me, they tell me that these are
desmienten a mí me dicen que estos son
nonsense,
tonterías
okay, I'll put my hand in the fire for a fact
vale pongo la mano en el fuego por hecho
because they're denying it, I can't
porque me lo desmienten no la puedo
put it in the fire, obviously, good
poner en el fuego evidentemente buenas
Javi, can you send my greetings to my aunt
Javi puedes mandarle un saludo a mi tía
Rosamel, forrito? Greetings from Chile, let's
rosamel forrito Saludos desde chile a
see if you want, I'll kiss them for you, Andy. Let's see, I can't. Let's
ver si quieres te los roso Andy A ver no
see, I can't put my hand in the
puedo A ver no puedo poner la mano en el
fire for this information, okay,
fuego por por estas informaciones vale
because of the fact that they
por el hecho de que a mí me lo
deny it to me, okay, because of the fact that they
desmientan vale por el hecho de que a mí
deny it to me, this rumor that Auron has
me desmientan este rumor de que auron
something with
tenga nada con
Paulet, they flatly deny it to me,
paulet a mí me lo desmienten
okay, what I
rotundamente vale lo que yo
believe, what I believe is that there's nothing,
creo lo que yo creo Es que no hay nada
based on how they've denied it to me and
por como me lo han desmentido y por
some data.  okay what I think is that there is
algunos datos vale lo que yo creo Es que
nothing now obviously
no hay nada ahora evidentemente
and obviously because I can't put my
e evidentemente por no puedo poner la
hand in the fire Hey okay what he
mano en el fuego Oye vale a mí lo que me
told me is that in fact he is still
dic es que no que de hecho sigue
friends with
teniendo amistad con los
both of them the best one wants to have something with him
dos el millor quiere tener algo con bí
for a long time It's not a joke what
desde hace tiempo No es broma a m lo que
pissed me off wasn't this tweet okay
que me mosqueado no fue este tweet vale
This tweet was posted after I
Este tweet lo lo puso después de que yo
released the exclusive because yeah
sacara la la exclusiva porque se se se
the wasp nest got a bit stirred right and they
movió un poco la avispero no y y le
were giving him more fuel No I
estaban dando como más más leña No yo
'm single stop [ __ ] with me and getting me
estoy soltera dejen de joderme y meterme
into gossip especially the multi-accounts
en chisme especialmente las multicuentas
that have nothing more to do than make
que no tienen nada más que hacer que
things up there are issues that
inventar cosas hay asuntos que deben
people should resolve for themselves and
resolver las personas por sí misma y
I'm sick of you getting me into things that
estoy harta de que me metan en cosas que
I have no reason to talk about or
yo no tengo por qué hablar o que
relating anything of mine with that
relacionen cualquier cosa mía con eso
find a life yourselves it's my networks and not
búsquense una vida son mis redes y no
everything I post has to do with a
todo lo que pongo tiene que ver con un
topic What are you referring to? You are referring to this
tema A qué se refiere se refiere a este
tweet that you
tweet que
deleted, I mean right when I uploaded the
borró o sea justo cuando yo subí el
video paulet tweeted this let's see if it's
vídeo paulet tuiteó esto a ver sí que es
true [ __ ] that pisses me off  you [ __ ] it
verdad [__] que me mosquea que te cagas
pisses me off it pisses you off this tweet I'm not
me mosquea que te caga este tweet no os
going to deny it
lo voy a negar
but I'm going to trust my source because what's
pero voy a confiar en mi fuente porque
going on Ah
pasa Ah
okay I trust my source and I think no
vale Confío en mi fuente y creo que no
but this isn't the account it's not the same
pero esta no es la cuenta no es la misma
Ah okay the screenshot wasn't verified a
Ah vale es que no estaba verificada la
kiss I'm weird this is that weird
beso yo es rarete este es que rarete es
this t has mocked me hyper
que este t me ha moqueado hyper eso lo
paulete tweeted that through the nauter flay no I don't
tuiteó paulete por la nauter flay no no
know Karime I don't think anyone has
lo sé Karime no creo que nadie haya
noticed nauter flay except the
hechado cuenta nauter flay menos los
usual four bad guys from Twitter
cuatro malillos de siempre de Twitter
and I'm telling you okay I mean I take
e ya os digo vale o sea me hago
responsibility for my words not for what
responsable de mis palabras no de lo que
you guys understand
ustedes entendáis
okay It's not that on Twitter it was already for
okay No es que en Twitter ya estaba
weeks on Twitter it wasn't
desde hace semanas en Twitter no estaba
on Twitter there were the rumors of
en Twitter estaba los rumores de la
people noticing this detail of
gente dándose cuenta de este detalle de
this other detail I'm giving you the
este otro detalle yo te estoy dando la
confirmation no but it's that today he said
confirmación no pero es que hoy ha dicho
that a sweatshirt that okay very good
que una sudadera que vale que muy bien
but I'm telling you that they broke up
pero que te estoy diciendo que han roto
okay And to me they flatly deny this
vale Y a mí Esto me lo desmienten
okay to me They
rotundamente vale a mí Esto me lo
flatly deny this and they tell me
desmienten rotundamente y Me comentan
no it's not
no
worth it  this is as far as I can
vale esto es hasta donde os puedo
read
leer
but it's true that they turn
pero de verdad es que le dan la vuelta a
everything around no but it's not on Twitter but it's that
todo no pero es que en Twitter no pero
you It's that this
es que tú Es que este esta cuenta de
Twitter account had said it before but let's
Twitter lo había dicho antes pero vamos
see that the Twitter account didn't
a ver que la cuenta de Twitter no es que
say it either they would confirm it if it
dicho tampoco te lo confirmarían si
were real let's see luare I think that I think they would
fuera real a ver luare yo creo que yo
n't
creo que no me lo
deny it if it were real I think they would
desmentir si fuera real yo creo
n't deny it they would
que no me lo desmin
say the way they did maybe they're
dirían de la forma en la que lo hicieron
fooling me okay But let's see
a lo mejor me engañan vale Pero a ver
one thing is that they fool me in
una cosa es que me engañen en
this okay I would understand the reasons but
en esto vale entendería los motivos pero
another thing is that they fool me in the
otra cosa es que me engañen en la
confirmation of the breakup okay I mean the
confirmación de la ruptura vale o sea la
breakup is okay without more
ruptura es vale sin más
Miami confirmed it to me Go [ __ ] yourself
Miami me lo confirmó Vete a la [__]
eat my
cómeme los
balls Javi
huevos Javi
WhatsApp
WhatsApp
okay Ah that gibel has created another
vale Ah que gibel se ha creado otra
account well let's see you've gotten
cuenta bueno a ver te me has adelantado
a
un
little ahead of me Hey but what is this guy about
poco Oye pero este tío de qué va este
this guy has just falsified
tío este tío acaba de falsear
a has just falsified a miniature
una acaba de falsear una una miniatura
of the salseria eh I mean this is
de la salsería eh o sea esto es
completely fake it's completely fake this eh
completamente
is completely fake let's see they have it
eh es completamente fake a ver lo han
but is it or not  is if the cat follows the
pero es o no es si le sigue el gato el
fuk
fuk
and of course this, I mean this is piracy
e de ento esto o sea esto es piratería
this is piracy
esto es piratería
okay this is pure piracy and let's see The
vale esto es piratería pura e a ver La
thing is that they've
Movida es que lo han
suspended it but it's not very clear to me
suspendido pero no me queda muy claro
why Because the fug is
por qué Porque el el fug le está echando
blaming
la culpa a
gibel that is his identity planting
gibel eso es su plantación de identidad
in fact this is criminal or rather this
de hecho esto es delictivo o seaa esto
is completely a crime eh could I
es completamente un delito eh podría
could report it eh I
podría denunciarlo eh
could report it to the
podría denunciarlo al
FBI they say that it is No man yes I
FBI dicen que sí es No hombre sí
understand that yes eh Let's see I don't know why they
entiendo que sí eh A ver no sé por qué
suspended it eh F is
lo han suspendido eh F está echando la
blaming
culpa a
roldier it would have to do with the twit crossing
roldier tendría que ver el cruce de twit
How did it go okay I don't know what power they can
Cómo ha ido vale No sé qué poder pueden
have Ah the verified eh is that already the
tener Ah el verificado eh es que ya el
verified before with the verified
verificado antes con el verificado
when I had ten When you had the
cuando tenía ten Cuando tenías el
verified they didn't have the balls to take down your
verificado no tenían [__] de tumbarte
account what happens is that the
una cuenta lo que pasa es que ya el
verified is not the same verified as
verificado no es el mismo verificado de
back then, I mean the verified before
aquel entonces o sea el verificado antes
if it was special and the accounts that
si era especial y las cuentas que
were verified on Twitter if it was
estaban verificadas en Twitter si la
carried out as a special department
llevaba como un departamento especial
by what was said no but of course Now
por lo que se decía no pero claro Ahora
no now the verified is no longer  that's what it
no ahora el verificado ya no es lo que
was now the verified ones that you pay
era ahora el verificado eses que pagues
a subscription and they put the icon there
una suscripción y te pongan el icono ahí
yes it is true that yes it is true
sí que es verdad que sí que es verdad
that to the people who are verified
que a la gente que somos verificados
real Okay and not the fake ones like for
reales Vale y no los falsos como por
example gibel who pays to pay
ejemplo gibel que paga para que paga
to be it by the date look you see it
para estarlo por la fecha mira lo veis
look by the date December 2021 you see it
mira por la fecha diciembre 2021 lo veis
by the date you can see that my
por la fecha se puede ver que mi
verified is from The Real ones well let's see
verificado es de Los Reales bueno a ver
several things happened several things happened
pasaron varias pasaron varias cosas
okay I don't know if it's maybe also
vale No sé si es que a lo mejor también
with what they messed up yesterday there's a
con la que liaron ayer por ahí Vaya un
bit of the issue of the reports and the funa and
poco el tema de los reportes y la funa y
so on yesterday they said some pretty funnable things
demás ayer dijeron cosas bastante
No I haven't seen the entire Stream I saw some
No no he visto todo el Stream vi algunos
pieces now I'm going to watch a couple of them
trozos ahora voy a ver un par de ellos
also here with you let's see I have
también aquí con ustedes a ver yo he
found jokes that for me are
encontrado chistes que para mí son
too
demasiado
heavy okay for example incai had been
pesados vale por ejemplo incai se había
very offended
ofendido mucho
eh Inc Kai had been very offended with
eh Inc Kai se había ofendido mucho con
this issue with the issue of the
este tema con el tema de que lo de lo
Hitler salute let's see each one is within their right
Hitler a ver cada uno está en su derecho
and I imagine that for personal reasons no
y me imagino que por cosas personales no
and each one is within their right to be
y cada uno está en su derecho a
offended by  whatever I want more than
ofenderse por lo que quiera yo más que
this they sent me clips of
esto a mí me me mandaron clip de
things that for me are a little out of
cosas que para mí está un poco fuera de
place in the sense jokes okay
lugar en el sentido bromas vale
Anyway we're going to see some changes
Igualmente vamos a ver algunos cambios
that they gave me okay Hi Javi I loved
que me dieron vale Hola Javi me encant
Chavo del Ocho I'm glad I'm glad
el del Chavo del o me alegro me alegro
because the truth is that it has a lot of work
porque la verdad que tien mucho curro
okay we're trying I'm not going to
vale estamos intentando no me voy a
give up okay I'm not going to give up at the
rendir vale no me voy a rendir en de
moment we're going to fight to try to
momento vamos a pelear en intentar
position it obviously it's going to cost
posicionarlo evidentemente va a costar
work because
trabajo porque
and because the channel has always had other
e porque el canal ha tenido siempre otra
themes okay the main channel I'm going to
temática vale el canal principal voy a
focus on more elaborate series I've already
enfocarlo en series más curradas ya lo
said it okay for example Jeffre that
he dicho vale por ejemplo de jeffre que
came up okay for example
surgió vale por ejemplo el juicio de
Johnny dep's trial okay
Johnny dep vale
eh
eh
now I'm trying to make a series
ahora estoy intentando hacer una serie
about Chavo del Ocho okay the first
sobre el Chavo del Ocho vale el primer
video I made didn't work too badly let's
videito que hice no funcionó muy mal a
see it's short but it didn't work too
ver está cortito pero no funcionó muy
bad the last one the truth is that it has been
mal el último la verdad es que ha sido
a pretty powerful puncture but I think that they
un pinchazo bastante potente pero creo
are videos that as
que son vídeos que conforme vayan
the days weeks years go by They may
pasando los días semanas años Pueden
continue to get visits So I'm going to
seguir entrándole visitas Así que voy a
continue working on that series
seguir trabajando en esa serie
and let's see if we can achieve it okay
y y a ver si si podemos lograrlo vale
[Music]
[Música]
mm the series that I'm going to do with Franeta
mm la serie que voy a hacer con franeta
in Thailand I'm going to upload it on the
en Tailandia la voy a subir en el
main page okay if it gets tense to
principal vale si se tensia a grabar
also record videos with Fran talking about
también vídeos con Fran hablando de
gossip they will be uploaded here to the salsería
salseos se subirán aquí a la salsería
okay
vale
eh more than anything it is to focus well on the
eh más que nada es enfocar bien las las
themes okay focus well on the
temáticas vale enfocar bien las
themes that's where it's going Well
temáticas por ahí va encaminado Bueno
I want I want to see a couple of camillos that I
quiero Quiero ver un par de camillos que
had here in the live of these
tuve aquí en el directo de esta
people Frank is very gossipy he loves he
gente Frank es bien chismoso le encanta
loves gossip the the Frank
le encanta el chisme el el Frank el
Frank defended me defended me when
Frank me defendió me defendió cuando
when what happened with the
cuando pasó lo
when more invited here friend Hey and
del cuando más invitado aquí amigo Oye y
why don't they bring Javi here too or doesn't he
por no traen al Javi también aquí o no
get along with any of you Ah with
se lleva con alguno de ustedes Ah con
Manche he told me he spoke to me Comanche When Comanche
manche me dijo me habló Comanche Cuándo
spoke to me this
me habló Comanche esta
morning he
mañana
spoke to me with Manche this morning I think it
me habló con manche esta mañana creo que
was he spoke to me to tell me that we
fue me habló para decirme que que
should do a live show you that we should do
hiciéramos un directo tú que hiciéramos
a live show he told me I told him that
un directo me dijo yo le he dicho que
whenever he wants obviously you want that he should
cuando quiera evidentemente queréis que
bring him tomorrow the day after to
lo queréis que lo traiga mañana pasado a
Comanche and we can chat a little about everything I have
Comanche y charlamos un poco de todo
some things that would be nice to
tengo algunas cosas que estarían guapas
talk about it with  Comanche is that Javi is from
hablarla con Comanche es que Javi es de
another
otra línea
timeline he is with Delox Nimu
temporal está con delox nimu
eh he the stutterer Raise your hand But
eh el el tartaja Levanta la mano Pero
why has he Raise your hand that they
por qué ha Levanta la mano que le han
asked him and why don't they bring Javi
preguntado y por qué no traen al Javi
here too or doesn't he get along with any of
también aquí o no se lleva con alguno de
you is that Javi is from another timeline
ustedes es que Javi es de otra línea
Ah he is with Delox Nimu is that we are
Ah está con delox nimu es que estamos
doing like like our Crew against
haciendo como como nuestra Crew contra
then Delox Nimu Javi you know let's see
luego delox nimu Javi sabes a ver
declaring himself misogynistic and sexist saying that
declararse misogino y machista decir que
women are all [ __ ] etcetera
las mujeres son todas put etcétera me
seems to me something more than jokes eh those in
parece algo más que bromas eh esas en
particular that they tell me no they are not the ones that
concreto que me dicen no no son las que
I have seen but if they have said it like that Yeah let's
yo he visto pero si la han dicho así Si
see it is that they are making jokes that I
a ver es que están haciendo bromas que
understand maybe they do it in
que entiendo a lo mejor que la hagan en
a private setting okay
un ámbito privado vale
but as many jokes as they are
pero por mu bromas que sean
eh As many jokes as they
eh Por mu bromas que
are, I don't know, I have seen things what about
sean yo que sé yo he visto cosas qué tal
But well eh I don't know what I'm telling you I
Pero bueno eh yo que sé qué te digo o
mean everyone shits whatever comes out of their
sea cada uno caga lo que le salga de la
dick no no I'm not going to say more let's see
[__] no no no vo decir más a ver a m a
me it's that I really dislike the stutterer okay
mí es que el tartaja me cae muy mal vale
Eh I have no problem with him to me
Eh no tengo ningún problema con él a mí
personally, he hasn't done
personalmente no me ha no me ha hecho
anything to me. I mean, literally, he hasn't
nada O sea literalmente a mí no me ha
done anything to me, I don't have any problem with
hecho nada no tengo ningún problema con
him, but I really dislike him, I really dislike him,
él pero me cae muy mal es que me cae muy
okay, I mean, yes,
mal vale o sea sí que hubo un tiempo en
at first I thought he was a
el que al principio me creía que era un
good guy, but then I saw his true colors and I did
buen chaval pero luego le vi el plumer y
n't like him, I mean, there were a few
no me no me gustó o sea hubo una serie
things that I saw that I didn't like,
de cosas que yo vi que no me gustaron
but like, things that I know, things that
pero en plan cosas que yo que sé cosas
when you've been doing this for a while,
que cuando llevas tiempo ya dedicándote
mm, I see things and I don't like them, okay,
mm veo cosas y no me gustan vale Y luego
and then, well, I don't know, it gets really heavy for me, I really dislike him, I have nothing against him, eh, I mean, I have nothing with him that's going very well for him and I don't wish him any harm and if at
muy bien y no le deseo nada malo y si en
some point I had to help
algún momento tuviera que echarle un
him out, I don't know, imagine if his
cable con yo que sé imagínate le
channel is suspended and I can retweet
suspenden el canal y yo puedo retuitear
his new account, I'm going to do it, okay, like what
su cuenta nueva lo voy a hacer vale como
happened now with Gibel, but I don't like him, damn it, I
ha pasado ahora con gibel pero no me cae
mean, that thing
bien [__] [__] o sea yo eso de eso de
with Ari and all that [ __ ] is like,
lo de Ari y toda la [__] esa es como
[ __ ] it, [ __ ], and that's it, but let's see, those are
[__] madre y ya está pero a ver eso son
personal opinions. It's okay. Maybe
opiniones personales No pasa nada A lo
I do too.  I don't like him, I don't
mejor yo también le caigo mal a él no lo
know, eh. I don't know this guy,
sé eh A este chico no lo conozco la
honestly. I don't know if I like him or not
verdad no sé si me puede caer bien o mal
because his videos are like very objective,
porque sus vídeos son como muy objetivos
no, and we have reacted and they are well-
no y hemos reaccionado y son vídeos bien
edited videos and such. I haven't seen him, I've barely
montados y tal no he visto no lo he
seen him talking in these live shows.
visto hablando en estos directos apenas
[Music]
[Música]
and I don't know if I like him or not, honestly. Okay,
y y no sé si me cae bien o mal la verdad
Uncle Shur. Let's see, I have
vale el el tío shur a ver yo he
criticized many things about Uncle Shur. Okay.
criticado muchas cosas del tío shur vale
And there are many things that I don't agree with
Y hay muchas cosas que no comparto con
him, but m I, Uncle Shur. It's that I think he's
él pero m Yo el tío shur Es que creo que
a good guy, I mean. I think
es un buen chaval o sea Es que creo que
Uncle Shur is a good person, honestly. And
es buena persona el tío shur la verdad Y
besides, well, [ __ ], there have been many years between
aparte pues [__] son muchos años
us, more or less, but I
nuestros más nuestros menos pero yo le
have a certain appreciation for him, I would say that I
tengo cierto aprecio yo diría que le
have a certain appreciation for him. The truth is. And also, I
tengo cierto aprecio La verdad Y además
think he's a good person despite there
que me parece buena persona a pesar de
being things that I don't agree with him or
que haya cosas que no comparta con él o
or things at work and all that stuff,
o movidas en el trabajo y todo el rollo
okay. But that's independent. He's
ese vale Pero eso es independiente el el
famous. He's funny, honestly. I do
famas el famas me hace gracia la verdad
n't dislike him, I think he's funny. The truth is. I don't dislike him. The truth is. I like
no me cae mal me hace gracia la verdad
him, okay. I
no me cae mal La verdad me cae bien vale
don't dislike him, but it's true.  eh I
no me cae mal pero sí que verdad que eh
said it here the day it came up okay there are
lo dije aquí el día que subió vale hay
some things that he has commented on his
algunas cosas que él ha comentado en su
Twitter and in his live streams that I don't
Twitter y en sus directos pues que no me
like about people that I appreciate without
gustan sobre gente que yo aprecio sin
further ado obviously I have no
más evidentemente no tengo ningún
problem with him and I think it shows
problema con él y creo que se nota
okay but man no it's not with it's not my
vale pero hombre no no es con no es mi
Crew okay I mean This is their Crew of them
Crew vale o sea Esta es su Crew de ellos
I have mine and that's it Okay but
yo tengo la mía y ya está Vale pero el
famas for example I like the
famas por ejemplo me cae en Gracia la
truth is I like the famas
verdad me cae en Gracia
but he's too funable he's too
pero es demasiado funable es demasiado
funable and there are things that he has said that I don't
funable y hay cosas que ha dicho que no
like one bit about Well I already
me gustan un pelo sobre Bueno ya las
said them the day that eh I mean about [ __ ] he
dije el día ese eh o sea sobre [__]
even put half a tweet supporting
puso incluso twit medio cap apoyando al
my doctor I [ __ ] on the [ __ ] How
al mis doctor me cago en la [__] Cómo se
can you How can you support
puede Cómo se puede apoyar a una persona
such a despicable person okay It's not because
tan despreciable vale Ya no es porque
they more or less agree with me you
estén más o menos de acuerdo con conmigo
understand I mean but because there are things
me entiendes o sea sino porque hay cosas
that I think should I think there are
que yo creo que debería yo creo que hay
things that should be unanimous or of the
cosas que deberían ser unánimes o de los
pathetic channels there are no
canales penosos no hay
more but well I have nothing
más pero bueno que no tengo nada en
against any of them none absolutely
contra de ninguno ninguno absolutamente
none but I don't like the cut in fact
ninguno pero el taje me cae mal de hecho
yes the
sí la
per is but that one but a  question is that
per es pero ese pero una pregunta esa es
a Crew that really hates each other or are they
una Crew que de verdad se odian o lo
doing it for mam that's it I don't
están haciendo por mam ya está yo no
have a problem with anyone I went out with that
tengo problema con nadie yo salí con eso
there you have Frank there the fixed one What does he say
ahí ties Frank ahí el fijado Qué dice
hello I'm the twet fixed says hello I'm
hola soy el twet fijado dice hola soy
gbel I'm Jer I like [ __ ] and
gbel Soy Jer me gusta la concha y a
sometimes the dick I [ __ ] for 40 and suck whatever
veces la pija culeo por 40 y mamo lo que
for 10 but apart from the fact that gibel
sea por 10 pero aparte que el gibel
is good gibel The good thing about him is that he
es bueno el gibel Lo bueno que tiene es
condemns koku with that he earns a
que condena a koku con eso gana
lot with that he earns Yes yes yes he condemns
mucho con eso gana Sí sí sí condena a
kzu a lot eh In fact
kzu muchísimo eh De hecho
eh the stutterer says that it's that
eh el tartaja dice que es que lo de czu
he hadn't found out about czu okay
él no se había enterado vale
e but apart from that the piece of
e pero es que aparte el el pedazo de
Shameless was the one with the most viewers
Sinvergüenza era el que más espectadores
the other day okay I was
tenía el otro día vale que yo estaba
here working doing other things and I
aquí trabajando haciendo otras cosas y
had the window not activated I mean you have to
tenía el window sin activar o sea hay
be a piece of [ __ ]
que ser pedazo de cabrón
eh You have to be a piece of [ __ ] for that
eh Hay que ser cabrón para eso
Well thank you very much
Bueno muchísimas
for
gracias por
40 says Valeria be careful with gibel
40 dice Valeria ten cuidado con gibel en
seriously he's kind of a hater and he was until
serio es medio hater y lo ha sido hasta
recently with you yeah s I know I know I mean that's what I'm telling
hace poco contigo sí s lo sé lo sé o sea
you be it I don't have  no
es lo que te digo sea no tengo ningún
problem with him And such But to make
problema con él Y tal Pero ya para hacer
a Crew for example at the moment no Hey
una Crew por ejemplo de momento no Oye a
maybe with time you will know but for
lo mejor con el tiempo sabes pero de
now respect and cordiality is enough
momento respeto y cordialidad vale
but I don't like him eh I like him
simplemente pero no me cae en Gracia eh
Although I know the
Me cae simpático Aunque sé los
comments he has made and that he has been
comentarios que ha hecho y que ha sido
a bit of a hater But well There is one that has gone too far
medio hater Pero bueno Hay alguno que se
eh There is some comment that has
ha pasado eh Hay algún comentario que se
gone too far and then this one that
ha pasado y luego está ha hecho que
mentioned I know a Bolivian
mencionan yo conozco a un boliviano
affiliated with c very good there is what happened
afiliado c muy bueno hay al lo que pasó
that still sticks in my
que me sigue me sigue quedando en la
head is that in the first Twitch
cabeza que es que en el primer Twitch
riv in the first squid Javi Oliveira
riv en el primer squid a Javi oliveira
They invited him and and They bathed him and he was left out
Lo invitaron y y Lo bañaron y quedó
and he was left out and then they
fuera y quedó fuera y después lo lo
invited him the second one they didn't invite him because he
invit al segundo no lo invitaban porque
says that Auron wanted to invite him but he
dice que auron lo quería invitar pero
is on a TT blacklist we
que est en una Lista negra de TT
invited the same as Ricky edited the shur
invitamos igual que Ricky edit el shur
Javier Martínez and I don't remember who
Javier Martínez y no me acuerdo quién
else was on the list that year I have
más estaba ese año en la lista yo tengo
I have the one who was passed the list alra
yo tengo al que le pasaron la lista alra
was to me or
fue a mí o
rather and I passed it to Auron because I
sea y yo se la pasé a auron porque le
said Hey you invited Javi Look at this
dije Oye tú invitaste a Javi Mira esto
They told me that they can't invite him
me han dicho que no lo pueden invitar
but it was a Rivals blacklist not from
pero era una Lista negra de Rivals no de
Twitch But I suppose that with the
Twitch Pero supongo que ya con la
disappearance of it has already disappeared or it continues to
desaparición de ya desapareció o sigue
disappear that blacklist because a
ya desapareció esa Lista negra porque
while ago I found out that they invited
hace rato me enteré que invitaron a
Javier Mtz to a Rivals eh organized by
Javier mtz a un Rivals eh organizado por
ot then And or rather it is already there or rather
ot entonces Y o sea ya está ahí o sea
but yes in fact it was even smaller
pero sí de hecho estaba hasta ma chica
On that list Uh yes the list Yes well it is
En esa lista Eh sí la lista Sí bueno es
a very small change let's see the list the
un pequeñísimo cambo a ver la lista la
list no longer exists the list is black
lista ya no existe la lista está negra
from Beto let's say no it does not exist anymore on
del el Beto digamos no no existe ya en
Twitch it was on Twitch rival okay the
en Twitch era en Twitch rival vale la
people from twit
gente de twit
rival I think that very related to the
rival yo creo que muy relacionado con la
people from twit Spain I'm not going to deceive you
gente de twit España no os voy a engañar
okay more than anything because of the fact that those of us
vale más que nada por el hecho de los
were there okay
que estbamos vale
[Music]
[Música]
m
m
javia the squid game it's not that I
javia lo juego del calamar no es que
was thinking something stutter he didn't say
estaba pensando una cosa tartaja no dijo
anything about you in the live I don't think he
nada sobre ti en el directo creo que no
said anything else that we don't get along and now we'll
dijo más nada que no nos llevamos y ya a
see but it's what I'm telling you either I don't have
ver pero es lo que te digo sea tampoco
a problem with him or anything like that I do
tengo un problema con él ni nada por el
n't like it point So the thing
estilo no me cae punto O sea que era
about the  list for that who
real lo de la lista para aquello quién
said the list didn't exist Karime
decía que no existia la lista Karime
but if I saw the list literally I mean I think it
pero si la lista la vi literalmente o
could be that I
sea creo que la la puede ser que la
gave the exclusive of the list I
exclusiva de la lista la diera
saw the list literally Javi
yo yo la lista la vi literalmente Javi
brings Comanche okay I'll tell him tomorrow
trae a Comanche vale se lo digo mañana
the list has passed I saw it literally I mean
ha pasado la lista yo la vi literalmente
literally I saw the screenshot of the
o sea literal yo vi la captura de la
list
lista
yes I didn't comment on it I always here not
sí no lo comenté yo siempre aquí no
always at the salsa bar
siempre en la salsería
Guay Dallas has uploaded a video
Guay Dallas ha subido un vídeo
of lady
de de dama
G How long is it if you're not very aware
G Cuánto dura si no estás muy al tanto
YouTube it lasts half an
YouTube dura media
hour it has
hora
several it has several it has several it
varios tiene
has several
varios tiene varios tiene varios
pieces let's see she just uploaded the video
trozos a veras acaba de subir el vídeo
obviously we're not going to see the whole thing
evidentemente no lo vamos a ver entero
okay but we're going to see some
vale pero sí que vamos a ver algún
trail vlo you guys Hey
trillo vlo ustedes Oye ya se le va ya se
Dallas's swelling is going away
le va bajando el hinchazón al Dallas
eh You'll see how in a
eh Ya veréis como dentro de un
year it looks really cool let's see the
año se nota bien papasote a ver el vídeo
whole video obviously you're going to see it there
entero evidentemente lo Vais a ver allí
Okay I'll watch it privately off
Ok yo lo veré también en privado off
Stream too But now I would like to see
Stream Pero ahora sí que me gustaría ver
a little not only Dallas's opinion
un poco no solamente la opinión de
itself It's that I think Dallas was
sí Es que creo que Dallas estaba de
traveling that's why it took a little while I'm
viaje por eso tard t poco que os Estoy
reading that  you're telling me like what does
leyendo que me estáis diciendo como qué
Teodoro say Javi you've fought with
tal dice Teodoro Javi te has peleado con
everyone just for criticizing Dallas
todo el mundo solo por criticar a Dallas
you don't have any friends left on YouTube it's
no te quedan amigos en YouTube es
embarrassing Javi Teodoro the one who is
vergonzoso Javi Teodoro el que el que es
embarrassing that he doesn't have friends on
vergonzoso que no tenga amigos en
YouTube But what kind of hter are you
YouTube Pero tú qué clase de hter eres
Javi do you want dicks or dicks
Javi quieres [__] o [__]
eh natural gas let's see Teodoro my friend
eh gas natural a ver Teodoro amigo mío
I have friends in real life
yo los amigos los tengo la vida real
handsome what I have here are people who
guapo yo aquí lo que tengo son gente que
work inside the computer
trabajan dentro del ordenador
Okay
Vale
friend connect with life go out to the
amigo conéctate con la vida sal a la
street
calle
XD I haven't called him hter because it
XD no lo he llamado como hter porque se
seemed to me like a mouse locked in
me ha hecho como un ratón encerrar en
a cage I mean he thinks I but apart from that it's
una jaula o sea cree que yo pero aparte
how is what he said last
es que cómo es lo que ha dicho último
that he made me thank you very much the last
que me ha hecho muchas gracias lo último
the last sentence is not embarrassing why is it embarrassing I
la última frase no es vergonzoso por qué
mean how many people are there who don't
es vergonzoso o sea cuánta gente hay que
have that don't get along with anyone I mean why do I have to
no tiene que no se lleva con nadie o sea
get along with anyone on
por qué me tengo que llevar con nadie de
YouTube Come on I get along with many but
YouTube Vamos me llevo con muchos pero
in a natural and cordial way some some some
de forma natural y cordial alguno
are friends okay
algunos algunos sí que son amigos vale
But who do I have to get along with if
Pero con quién me tengo que llevar si
I'm here working
estoy aquí trabajando
colleague embarrassing  Javi Okay, that's it
colega vergonzoso Javi Bueno pues ya
Teodoro Well if you're embarrassed you
está Teodoro Pues si te da vergüenza
know where to go
ya sabe dónde ir
listen to me leave it, it'll be a kid
escúchame dejarlo será un crío A ver
Let's see Dallas' opinion and
vamos a ver la la opinión de Dallas y
above all and above all because lady G
sobre todo y sobre todo porque dama G le
sent him some messages I have to give you
mandó algunos mensajes os tengo que dar
an exclusive now I'm going to see this
una exclusiva ahora voy a ver este
piece I'm going to see some pieces what
trozo voy a ver un trocillos
Jer did I'll leave for the news I'm not
lo de Jer ya lo dejo para noticieros no
going to watch it now Okay I'm going to see this and I'm going I'm giving
lo voy a ver ahora Vale Voy a ver esto y
you the exclusive and I'm
y ya me voy os doy la exclusiva y ya me
going okay I have to give you two
voy vale os tengo que dar dos
exclusives that I'm going to give in an
exclusivas que la voy a dar en un
extract
extracto
okay perfectly right but
vale ricamente la razón pero
definitely rejecting it will surely take it
definitivamente el rechazarlo seguro que
away from you because you have to
te la quita porque algo Tienes que
hide something When this situation happened I
ocultar Cuando ocurrió esta situación yo
published a tweet which is this one here Oh
publiqué un tweet que es este de aquí Ah
okay just defined what a
vale acaba de definir lo que es un
debate is accept it or not here on YouTube
debate aceptarlo o no aquí en YouTube
I understand and in which I basically commented that
entiendo y en el que básicamente comenté
this was the definitive end of this
que este era el fin definitivo de esta
lady well damage had me
señora pues bien damage me tenía
blocked just before I published
bloqueado justo antes de yo publicar
this tweet I had it like three
este twet me tenía me cae como tres
kicks in the stomach lady G I'm
patadas en el estómago la dama G estoy
seeing there the face and the look with
viendo ahí la cara y la mirada con con
the smile that is looking at Dallas and
la sonrisa que está mirando a Dallas y
me  it makes me feel terrible it makes me feel
me cae fatal me cae
terrible do you remember the debate, I mean do you
fatal os acordáis del debate o sea os
remember when oh I want to see something else
acordáis cuando ay Quiero ver otra cosa
on Plex so I don't forget to remind you do you
de plex que no se me olvide recordármelo
remember in the debate because of the face
os acordáis en el debate por la cara
pedophile
pedófilo
pedophile dude is a really bad person eh really
pedófilo tío es una malísima persona eh
bad
malísima
person blocked on Twitter and I know
persona bloqueado en Twitter y lo sé
because I went to look at his profile I don't know what
porque fui a mirar su perfil no sé qué
screenshot of this he is freaking out he is freaking out
captura de esto está de los nervios está
but believe me he really
de los nervios pero creedme de verdad me
had me 100% blocked in fact I mentioned the
tenía 100% bloqueado de hecho menci los
private messages that she sent me on
mensajes privados que ella me mandó en
Twitter that I hadn't been able to see until
Twitter que no había podido ver hasta
now and what she did was respond to me
ahora y lo que hizo ella fue responderme
trying to do damage control
intentando hacer control de daños
saying I have reported that girl
diciendo tengo denunciada a esa chica
the evidence I have of her abuse is
las pruebas que tengo de su abuso son
huge spoiler her evidence has
enormes spoiler sus pruebas no tienen
absolutely nothing to do with anything what she's
absolutamente nada que ver con nada lo
basically saying is that the
que hace básicamente es decir que la
girl is very toxic that she is very bad that
chica es muy tóxica que es muy mala que
she has insulted her that she has said ugly things to her
la ha insultado que le ha dicho cosas
that you must be it could be Yes yes yes the
feas que lo serás puede ser Sí sí si la
girl You could see that what it was She had a
chica Se le veía que que era Tenía una
little attitude let's say she herself didn't
actitud un poco vamos ella misma no lo
recognize it here when we interviewed her
reconoció aquí cuando la entrevistamos
but it doesn't take away what what what
pero es no quita lo que lo que lo que
she wants that  remove or rather look at what she's
ella quiere que quite o sea fíjate tú lo
doing with her nerves
que está haciendo con los nervios
she commented on my video of the interview with
comentó en mi vídeo de la entrevista a
the girl eh she unblocked dala She
la chica eh desbloqueó a dala Le
wrote to him She wrote to him through
escribió Le escribió por
mdz blah blah Yes very nice but the thing is that
mdz bla bla Sí muy bonito pero es que
one thing doesn't take away from the fact that she wants to report herself
una cosa no quita quiere denunciar ella
before the other reports her
antes que la otra le denuncie a ella
when the other has said that she is not going to
cuando la otra ha dicho que no la va a
report her because those are things that
denunciar porque son cosas que no se
cannot be proven to the other if I walk down the
pueden probar a la otra si yo voy por la
street and someone starts to I don't know
calle y alguien se pone a no sé
insult me ​​and then I go and
insultarme y yo luego cojo y le doy un
punch them in the face both actions are
puñetazo en la cara ambas acciones son
true not because that person
verdad no por esa persona haberme
insulted me previously it turns out that I
insultado previamente resulta que yo la
really punched that is a lie
verdad un puñetazo eso es mentira
magically you basically what you do
mágicamente yos básicamente lo que hace
divert attention to basically
desviar la atención para básicamente
throw dirt on your reputation and
tirar tierra encima de su reputación y
pretend that for that reason So he is
fingir que por esa razón Entonces ya es
innocent now it's Dallas cried at the end of that
inocente es Dallas lloró al final de ese
debate from the frustration that
debate de la frustración que le hizo
that chick put him through dasas exploded really big
pasar esa tipa dasas explotó bien tocho
that was not a debate that I then went up
ese no fue un debate que yo luego me sub
to him to cheer him up a
con él a animarlo un
little there is a controversy that came out I don't know if you
poco hay una polémica que salió no sé si
have seen it he brought it out  gossip
la habéis visto la ha sacado chisme
youtuber saying that you were the one who
youtubero diciendo que eras tú el que le
had asked him for a kiss cheer up or something like that
habías pedido un beso animo o algo así
Oh it's true What happened there
Oh es verdad Qué pasó
I nmo yes I think I did ask him for
ahí yo a nmo sí creo que le lleg a pedir
a kiss once
un beso una
[Laughs]
[Risas]
loe it my father added it out of nowhere It's not that
vez loe lo mi padre adó de la nada No es
that silence of two or three seconds, let's
que ese silencio de dos o TR segundos ya
go if it comes to say that we wouldn't
vamos si llega a deí que no le Le
have told him that he was lying
hubiéramos dicho que estaba mintiendo
stupid This is the practice that I was
estúpido Esta es la práctica que iba
doing for a long time really
haciendo mucho tiempo damage de verdad
vomitous damage thanks to the fact that you also
vomitivo gracias a que igualmente me
unblock me I could enter his profile
desbloqueas se pude entrar en su perfil
and see what he had sent me during
y ver lo que me había mandado durante
all these years and I hadn't even
todos estos años y yo ni siquiera lo
seen it I want you to see that this is
había visto quiero que veáis que esto es
strong eh in 2019 here was the beginning of
fuerte eh en 2019 aquí fue el inicio de
saying join the broadcast with
diciendo entra a la transmisión con
great pleasure how do we do it I never
mucho gusto como la hacemos nunca
responded to this in September 2021 he
respondí a esto en septiembre 2021 me
told me Dallas I know that you and I had a
dijo Dallas sé que tú y yo tuvimos un
problem a problem from
problema un problema del
21 the problem is with you mentally I didn't
21 el problema lo tienes tú mental yo no
have any problem with you but it's not
tuve ningún problema contigo pero no es
true that I said that to that girl, I
verdad que yo le dije eso a esa chica o
mean, I mean this was another controversy in which
sea o sea esto era otra polémica en la
before Dalas was
que antes de que Dalas estuviera
making a video for him I know that you  and I had
haciéndole vídeo sé que tú y yo tuvimos
a problem says man let's see you started
un problema dice hombre a ver te pusiste
yelling pedophile at me on a video call
a gritarme pedófilo en una videollamada
You'll tell me
Tú me dirás
no but I mean before Dalas
no pero o sea antes de que Dalas la
fune goes running to put the bandage
fune va corriendo a a poner la venda
before the wound you how pathetic you can
antes que la herida tú qué patética podr
be a lot that I really dislike the d
ser mucha que me cae muy mal la d
also eh today I am today I am very
también eh hoy estoy hoy estoy muy
negative with people on the internet I
negativo con la gente de internet Me cae
really dislike dam G How do you all dislike her I
muy mal dam G Cómo os cae a ustedes a mí
really dislike things but I wasn't
me cae muy mal cosas pero no fui
transphobic with her herself story
transfóbica con ella ella misma histor
is that it just came to mind that
es que se me acaba de venir a la mente
video call eh how disgusting God
la la videollamada esa eh qué asco Dios
[ __ ] video call eh how
putísima videollamada eh qué
unpleasant eh nobody knew I was trans
desagradable eh nad sabía que era trans
more than her and my ex didn't know I was
más que ella y mi ex no sabía que era
trans In fact I didn't argue with her anyway I
trans De hecho yo no discutí con ella en
never did about this
fin paredo nunca hice al respecto a este
issue but look at that September
tema pero fijaos que en septiembre de
2021 she was trying to contact me to
2021 está intentando contactarme para
try again to do damage control
intentar de nuevo hacer control de daños
with me and precisely when I posted this
conmigo y precisamente cuando puse este
tweet she unblocked me then I was able to see the
tweet me desbloqueó entonces pude ver
entire previous one and when she unblocked me
todo el anterior y cuando me desbloqueó
she wrote the following to me Dallas I have
me escribió lo siguiente Dallas tengo
a lot of proof that she is my
muchas pruebas de que ella es mi
abuser Yeah sure go tell
abusadora Sí claro vete contar historia
someone else's story for real Teach me how to play
otra persona de verdad Enséñame a jugar
the abused feminist card here
la carta aquí de feminista abusada
after they accused you with
después de que te han acusado a ti con
plenty of reasons to accuse you
razones de sobra para acusarte después
after you publicly said I'd rather
de que tú dijeras públicamente prefiero
believe a possible victim than a
creerme A una posible víctima que un
possible accuser I'd rather defend a
posible acusador prefiero defender a una
possible victim than a possible vador and
posible víctima que a un posible vador y
now you pretend to accuse her of her
ahora pretendes tú acusar a ella de ella
abusing you cuz You have no reason
abusar a ti cu No tienes ninguna razón
to say that I'm really sorry look look I
para decir eso De verdad penos mira mira
know we don't have a good history
sé que no tenemos un buen historiala
look pay attention to this Look I'm
mira mira atentos a esto Mira la estoy
reporting her and I'm going to win because I have
denunciando y voy a ganar porque tengo
more than 100 gigabytes of evidence of some
más de 100 gigas de pruebas de una
pretty brutal violence of course 100
violencia bastante brutal claro 100
gigabytes That means the evidence
gigas Eso quiere decir que las pruebas
is very strong man of course Let's see you
Son muy fuertes hombre claro A ver tú le
can put The Lion King
puedes meter al disco duro El rey león
in HD on the hard drive okay if you want you can
en HD vale si tú quieres se lo puedes
put it in Blu-ray quality and it weighs
meter en calidad blu-ray y pesa más
even more let's see let's see This is
todavía vamos a ver vamos a ver Esto es
literally the one about the mortgages
literalmente la la de las hipotecas
denouncing delox and the 8 gigabytes that he
denunciando al delox y los 8 gigas que
never showed I mean [ __ ] 100 Gb put it
nunca mostró o sea [__] 100 Gb pónmelo
on the screen put it on me  on screen here in
en pantalla pónmelo en pantalla aquí en
Stream in the lowest quality that weighs
Stream en la más baja calidad que pese
less really what a [ __ ] joke eh what a
menos de verdad qué [__] payasada eh qué
[ __ ] joke one interaction and it was
putísima payasada una interacción y fue
the end of your career What a
el final de tu carrera Cómo que
history how are you going to call history a
historial cómo le vas a llamar historial
thing anyway but I can really
al una cosa en fin pero de verdad puedo
prove that the girl is extremely
demostrar que la chica es extremadamente
violent I am reporting her and I am going to
violenta la estoy denunciando y voy a
win because I have more than 100 gigabytes of
ganar porque tengo más de 100 gigas de
evidence of some pretty brutal violence I
pruebas de una violencia bastante brutal
am reporting her and I am going to win what
la estoy denunciando y voy a ganar lo
Teo for my personal safety damage
que Teo por mi seguridad personal damage
Let me explain something to you okay if you
Déjame explicarte una cosita vale que
have 100 gigabytes of evidence doesn't mean you
tengas 100 gigas de pruebas no significa
have a lot it means that your
que tengas muchas significa que tu
compression is pathetic learn to compress
compresión da pena aprende a comprimir
videos and photos and maybe
los vídeos y las fotos y a lo mejor
these 10 GB become 100 gig
estos 10 GB se convierten en 100 gig
but 100 GB is an outrage eh I mean
pero 100 GB es una barbaridad eh o sea
100 GB saving screenshots and
100 GB guardando captura de pantalla y
such is 100 GB It's a very beastly
tal es 100 gb Es un es muy bestia
not 100 GB but that one has put in there
no 100 GB pero esa esa le ha metido ahí
100% GTA 6 I mean there's no more eh 100
100% el GTA 6 o sea no hay más eh 100
GBas has gone a bit too far
gbas se ha pasado un poco
uh 500 megabytes really pale anyway as
eh 500 megas de verdad paléo en fin como
you can see this because I never
podéis ver esto pues nunca le I a
answered her but where I did answer her was
responder pero donde sí le respondí fue
on Instagram and this was the conversation
en Instagram y esta fue la conversación
that we had through Instagram
que tuvimos a través de Instagram
Instagram where I tried to see if she was
Instagram donde intenté ver a ver si
really going to show me that evidence that she
realmente me iba Mostrar esas pruebas
already said so much that oh I can
que tanto ya decía que ay os puedo
prove to you I don't know what I don't know How many That
demostrar no sé qué no s Cuántos Que
obviously I have not proven
obviamente no he demostrado
absolutely anything here I don't know why There is
absolutamente nada aquí no sé por qué
a big space But this is the
Hay un gran espacio Pero esto es el
beginning of the conversation on March 13,
inicio de la conversación el 13 de marzo
2019 when she mentions the stories
de 2019 cuando me menciona las historias
basically insulting me that you have
básicamente insultándome que habéis
seen and here she writes to me saying Hey
visto y aquí me escribe diciendo Hey
Dallas I know we don't have a good
Dallas sé que no tenemos un buen
history but that girl is my
historial pero esa chica es mi
abuser I literally have more than
violentador literalmente tengo más de
100 GB of evidence or she sees you with the
100 gbas de pruebas o te ve con la
nonsense of the gigs when she
tontería de los gigas cuando no
literally does not prove anything and I say
demuestra literalmente nada y le digo
Hello How are you And she says Hello Fine and
Hola Cómo estás Y me dice Hello Bien y
you uh By the way this is quite curious
tú eh Por cierto esto bastante curioso
that you see it, I never even answered
que lo veáis nunca siquiera le respondí
a single message but she really
un solo mensaje pero ella bien que se
dedicated herself to saying publicly that I
dedicaba a decir públicamente que yo le
sent her photos
mandaba fotos
you would have liked it if I had at least
ya te hubiera gustado que yo siquiera te
sent you Oh okay heo it's Twitter  I don't
mandase Ah vale que heo es Twitter no
know it's Twitter I understand not a Good
heo es Twitter entiendo no un Buenos
morning princess would you like my goodness
días princesa ya te gustaría madre mía
the Clown and I said okay okay Right now
la Clown y le dije bien bien Ahora mismo
on a trip but I'll be back soon your
de viaje pero volveré en breve tu
ex-friend as you know offered me that she's
examiga como ya sabrás me ofreció que
willing to do a one-on-one
está dispuesta a hacer un cara a cara
with me as a moderator I recommend that you
conmigo de moderador Yo te recomiendo
accept or you'll come across as a
que aceptes o quedarás como una
liar And it's like you have something to
mentirosa Y como que tienes algo que
hide So if you want to deny
ocultar Así que si quieres desmentir
something now is your chance Yes yes the
algo ahora es tu oportunidad Sí sí la
girl told it here fixed the answer she
chica lo contó aquí fijos la respuesta
gives is the stupidest thing right I
que hace es la cosa más estúpida verdad
'm talking to a politician it's
estoy hablando con un político es
totally ridiculous and he tells me I have
totalmente ridículo y me dice yo tengo
a criminal complaint usually kills to say
una denuncia penal suele matar decir
false complaint against her For
denuncia fal contra ella
4 months now for harassment Severe
Desde hace 4 meses por acoso Severo
doxing threats defamation and damage to
doxing amenazas difamación y daño a la
morals Well apparently the girl yes it is
moral bien al parecer la chica sí que es
true that she has said many insults to
verdad que le ha dicho muchos insultos a
her and that on some occasions she has also
ella y que en alguna ocasión también ha
threatened in a certain way but again
amenazado de cierta manera pero de nuevo
one thing does not take away from the other and it is
una cosa no quita la otra y es
totally irrelevant let's see how you
totalmente irrelevante a ver cómo lo
understand it irrelevant like no it is not
entiendes irre relevante como no no es
no let's see irrelevant or rather in the
no es a ver irrelevante o sea en el
sense that it does not take away from what
sentido de que no quita de lo que la
the other is accusing her of okay or rather
está acusando la otra vale o sea es
their story is relevant  two as
relevante la historia de ellas dos como
such no Hey look this one did another to me and
tal no Oye pues mira esta me hizo otro y
then the behavior is Well
luego el comportamiento esta Pues
your career has also gotten a little out of hand I'm looking for a
tu carrera Estoy buscando una orden de
restraining order and that he can't look for me look
restricción y que no pueda buscarme mira
like Ricky Eddy like Ricky Eddy
como el Ricky Eddy como el Ricky Eddy
anymore or anyone I know for M
más ni a nadie de mis conocidos para M
is looking for a restraining order
está buscando una orden de restrinción
it's a circus for me it's my
es un circo para mí es mi seguridad
personal safety and the most pertinent thing is that it is
personal y lo más pertinente es que
resolved legally first and I
primero se resuelve legalmente y yo le
tell him that is not going to happen and that complaint is
digo eso no va a suceder y esa denuncia
not going to go anywhere the pertinent thing
no va a ir a ningún lado lo pertinente
is that you confront him face to face
es que lo enfrentes en un cara a cara
with a moderator me in this case and that
con un moderador yo en este caso y que
each one exposes their points if you reject it they will
cada uno exponga sus puntos si rechazas
see it as if you are hiding
lo van a ver como que estás ocultando
things and that you are afraid and
las cosas y que tienes miedo y
evidently And it is like that it is like that
evidentemente Y es que es así es así
but if you only have to look at the
pero si solamente hay que ver el
behavior not accept it you can see that it is
comportamiento no aceptar se ve que va
direct and without fear in your hand it is you
de frente y sin miedo en tu mano está
end up exulting your public image if
terminas de exultar tu imagen pública si
you reject this debate spoiler he did it and you are
rechazas este debate spoiler lo hizo y
going to see the excuses because it is
Vais a ver las excusas porque verdad es
disgustingly pathetic true I was
asquerosamente patético verad me dio
ashamed jena to read it again more by the
vergüenza jena leerla otra vez más por
way this garbage excuse  remember
cierto esta basura de excusa me recuerda
The same garbage that the rook did I don't know
La misma basura que hizo el rook no sé
if of course it's literal it's literal
si claro es que es literal es que es
literal imo you remember that the
literal literals imo acordáis que el
clown started saying I can't do one I have to
payaso se puso a decir no puedo hacer un
tell you an exclusive in
tengo que contaros una exclusiva dentro
a few minutes okay as soon as I finish
de unos minutos vale en cuanto termine
watching this video tell you why since
de ver este vídeo te contas porque
an ozen of distancing yes what a
puesto una ozen de alejamiento sí menudo
clown really the classic of the
payaso de verdad la clásica de los
cowards and googi answers me the complaint
cobardes y googi me responde la denuncia
against her it is becoming
contra ella se está volviendo
collaborative But what are you saying what do you think
colaborativa Pero qué dices qué te crees
a complaint is a YouTube channel you
que es una denuncia un canal de YouTube
really have no idea what you're
de verdad no tienes ni idea lo que estás
saying a criminal complaint for a case
diciendo una denuncia penal por un caso
of harassment it cannot magically become collaborative it's that
de acoso no se puede volver colaborativo
nonsense I doubt she
mágicamente es que es una tontería dudo
even filed a complaint
siquiera de que haya puesto una denuncia
at all this one has seen many
en absoluto esta se ha visto muchas
movies and now she has seen some
películas y ahora ha visto alguna
collaborative movie A lot of her victims appeared
colaborativa Salieron un montón de sus
[ __ ] clown of the balls eh I mean
puñetera payasa de los [__] eh o sea
but [ __ ] clown of the balls a
pero puñetera payasa de los [__] una
collaborative complaint Yeah man a
denuncia colaborativa Sí hombre un
crowdfunding there you have to
crowdfunding hay hay que hay que hay que
be a clown
ser payasa
eh You have to be a
eh Hay que ser
clown You have to be a
payasa Hay que ser
clown
payasín
says the mother who gave birth to me with YouTube
dice la madre que me parió con YouTube
eh the  mother who
eh la madre que me
gave birth to me lady town
parió dama pueblo
total I have an exclusive well two I'll
total tengo una exclusiva bueno dos os
tell you about it in this video
la comento en este vídeo
okay point number one
vale punto número
point number one first
punto número uno primero
the poster the exclusive poster the
el cartel el cartel de exclusiva el
exclusive poster okay I have to
cartel de exclusiva vale me tengo que
invent a dance like the haaka okay let's
inventar un baile como la haaka vale a
see like It's just a question but just out of
ver like Es que una pregunta pero solo
curiosity before I tell you about the
por curiosidad antes de comentaros la
exclusive okay one Like if you condemn
exclusiva vale uno Like si condenas a
Goku dislike if you don't
Goku dislike si no lo
condemn him Javi
condenas Javi
is very good
es buenísimo
eh comment if Javi is God Javi Go Javi
eh comentari si Javi es God Javi Go Javi
is God
es God
okay
vale
exclusive number one There are two exclusives
exclusiva número uno Son dos exclusivas
about Ricky edit well or at least
sobre Ricky edit bueno o por lo menos
related to him okay eh and there was a
relacionadas con él vale eh y había una
third one related to him but it's not
tercera relacionada con él pero que no
directly his things as they are and he's not to
es suya directamente las cosas como son
blame for anything okay but it's that I have
ni tiene culpa de nada vale pero me es
n't been able to confirm it and then
que no la he podido confirmar y entonces
since I haven't been able to eh Since I haven't been
como no la he podido eh Como no la he
able to confirm it then no Let's see apart it's
podido confirmar pues no A ver aparte es
a delicate and ugly subject m about a
un tema delicado y feo m sobre un
supposed video of Ali doing I don't know
supuesto vídeo del Ali haciendo No sé
what that is leaked okay
qué que sea filtrado vale
m I don't know exactly what I have
m No sé exactamente de lo
n't seen the video and and I can't
que no he visto el vídeo y y no puedo
tell you if I haven't seen it okay and I don't
comentaros si no lo he visto vale ni lo
want to see it I prefer not to see it warning a
quiero ver prefiero no verlo aviso un
kiss okay but yes it is true that there is
beso vale pero sí que es verdad que hay
one thing I have to tell you
una cosa que os tengo que comentar
okay this
vale este
Thursday it
jueves se
premieres at
estrena a las
no fear of success episode 27 Ricky
sin miedo al éxito episodio 27 Ricky
edit I'll tell you the
edit os digo el
title Javi yes it's true I
título Javi sí es verdad yo te lo
confirm it a kiss a kiss to everyone I'll tell you
confirmo un beso un beso a todos os digo
the title okay the
el título vale el
title I mean
título
that video has leaked no but
o sea se ha filtrado ese vídeo no pero
What is an only F video I imagine no
Qué es un vídeo de only F me imagino no
Javi you're all Flame kiss fire fire fire a
Javi estás todo Flama bes fuego fuego
kiss a kiss I mean yes it has
fuego un beso un beso o sea sí se ha
leaked no but why Because it's one
filtrado no pero eso por qué Porque es
of those that leaks no my goodness well yes it
de los que se filtra no madre mía pues
is as they have described it to me my goodness
si es como me lo han descrito madre mía
But anyway we'll talk about
Pero bueno ya hablaremos de
that the title of Thursday's podcast by
eso el título del podcast del jueves de
Ricky edit in no fear of
Ricky edit en sin miedo al
success the truth about Ali Dallas and the
éxito la verdad sobre Ali Dallas y los
eslam potop potón potop
eslam potop potón potop
potón the truth about Lali Dallas and the
potón la verdad sobre Lali Dallas y los
eslam he's
eslam
going to talk at length about
va a hablar largo y tendido sobre el
Ali and he's going to talk about well he's going to
Ali y va a hablar sobre bueno va a
explain he's going to explain we'll see
explicar va a explicar ya veremos a ver
the explanation I'd love to hear it
la explicación me encantará escucharla
uh about Dallas' restraining order
eh sobre la orden de alejamiento de
okay he's going to talk about that
vale va a hablar sobre esa orden de
restraining order supposed
alejamiento supuesta orden de
restraining order that he says he puts on her
alejamiento que él dice que le pone en
Dallas okay uh Well  it will probably be a
la Dallas vale eh Bueno será un podcast
fun podcast okay delos will be
seguramente divertido vale delos estará
here soon when are the
por aquí dentro de poco el cuándo son
esan Hey the eslan when are they are already
los esan Oye los eslan cuándo son son ya
these days no eh
estos días no eh
delox goes to the hlan what I don't remember
delox va a los hlan lo que no me acuerdo
What days are losan in the end they weren't in the
Qué días son losan al final no quedaron
14th in the end the elan or is
en en el 14 al final los elan o sigue en
the 16th or
pie el 16 o
17th still on well The thing is that the 14th in the
17 bueno El caso es que el caso el 14 al
end no The thing is that delox is going to be
final no El caso es que delox va a estar
at the hland and then he will come here
por los hland y después vendrá para acá
and we will be commenting on all these
y estaremos comentando todas estas
little things after the podcast okay And
cosillas des después del podcast vale Y
well I also had to tell you
bueno pues también tenía que comentaros
a little bit of something no I'm not going to tell you much
un poco algo no no os voy a contar mucho
okay let's
vale vamos a
wait a few days just okay to
esperar unos días solamente vale para
comment on it already well
comentarlo ya bien del
but it was already the trial of the
todo pero ya fue el el juicio de el
trial of tudor the trial of tudor
juicio de tudor el juicio de tudor ya
was already Javi thinks that Franco ten
fue Javi opina de que Franco ten
tenaglia shat himself I don't know What is that
tenaglia se [__] no s Qué es
Javi what do you think that Franco tenaglia
eso Javi qué opina de que Franco
shat himself I don't know that I don't know
tenaglia se [__] encima no sé que no sé
who it is what you missed is that
quién es lo que te perdiste es que
Comanche confirmed no no no I didn't
Comanche confirmó no no no me lo he
miss it gibel I didn't  I've lost big I
perdido gibel no me lo he perdido gordo
saw it I saw it I saw it I saw you've stayed
lo vi lo vi lo vi lo vi te has quedado
you don't deserve it pay for the
no te lo mereces paga la licencia del
Wind license pay for the
Wind paga la licencia de
Windom license eh it was the Tudor trial okay I
windom eh fue el juicio de tudor vale No
can't tell you
puedo comentaros
much honestly it's that I don't want to let's
mucho sinceramente es que no quiero a
see it was the trial and they're waiting for the
ver fue el juicio y están esperando a
verdict
que salga sentencia
Okay when the verdict comes out Well
Vale cuando salga la sentencia Pues
obviously we'll comment a little more
evidentemente comentaremos un poco más
but But
pero Pero bueno
basically basically I'm
básicamente básicamente solamente es que
only going to tell you that it was the
os voy a decir solamente que ha sido el
trial the only thing I'm going to tell you is
juicio lo único que os voy a decir es
that it was the trial and man well
que ha sido el juicio y que hombre pues
I think that I think that I
yo
think it went as it
que yo creo que ha ido como como como
had to go simply
tenía que ir simplemente
I think that it went as it had to go out
yo creo que ha ido como tenía que salir
without further ado okay that's it I'm going to read up to
sin más vale es lo el voy a leer hasta
here because I don't want to tell you or
aquí porque es que no quiero deciros ni
Hey, this one is going to lose it or the other one is going to
Oye pues lo va a perder este o lo va a
lose it because [ __ ] we're going to
perder la otra porque [__] vamos a
let justice pronounce itself and
dejar que la justicia se pronuncie y en
based on and based on what comes out we'll
base a y en base a lo que salga ya
comment okay but yes I can
comentaremos vale pero sí que os puedo
tell you that man that more or less I have
decir que hombre que más o menos Tengo
information about how it happened but it
información de de cómo transcurrió pero
's a delicate subject Okay then we're going to be
es un tema delicado Vale entonces vamos
cautious and we're going to
a vamos a tener prudencia y vamos a
wait  see what it is what it is what's
esperar a ver qué es lo que qué es lo
happening
que pasa
okay fighter from Jordi's evening and it's that I
vale luchador de la velada de Jordi y es
already told you at the beginning of the
que ya os he dicho al principio del
live that I'm really sticky
directo que de ese tema yo pegaísima
eh really sticky really [ __ ] Calime
eh pegadisimo pegadisimo
sent me something
[__] me me ha mandado calime una cosa
that I think is going to be powerful eh Let's
que creo que va a estar potente eh A
see and and and and and and and and look look Gema
ver y y y y y y y y mira mira Gema
[ __ ] How scary you I'm freaking out
[__] Qué miedo tú estoy flipando
[ __ ] my first sensation was [ __ ] my
[__] mi primera sensación ha sido
first sensation was How
[__] mi primera sensación ha sido Qué
scary you [ __ ] Why [ __ ] I can't
miedo tú cuernos Por qué [__] no me lo
believe it [ __ ] between the glasses the
creer [__] entre las gafas las alas
black wings bua it's a sensation between
negras bua es una sensación entre entre
surprise and fear at the same time eh
sorpresa y miedo a la vez eh
No no but no no
No no pero no no
no but if you didn't send me this it
no pero si no me has mandado lo de esto
's the Juan
es lo de Juan
Guarnizo thing about how great Juan Gref sees
guarnizo de qué grande Juan gref ve a
Juan in Spain and says this about the [ __ ]
Juan en España y dice esto de los ostia
that Juan Guarnizo is in the elan well he's
que Juan guarnizo está en los elan bueno
not in the hlan he said no
no está en los hlan ha dicho que no
well let's see in all honesty Juan
bueno a ver en en honor a la verdad Juan
Guarnizo what he said was that unless he
guarnizo lo que dijo fue que a no ser
had to come to Spain for something at
que tuviera que venir a España para algo
King he wouldn't go to Los
de la King no iría a Los
eslan I  I think Juan Guarnizo is going to Losan,
eslan yo creo que Juan guarnizo va losan
eh, a fighter from Jordi's evening, he didn't
eh luchador de velada de Jordi no
repeat the fight for the dollar, I mean, I would
repitió pelea por dólar o sea se
bet it's that I don't know it's that you already
apostaría es que no lo sé es que ya
know that I those
sabéis que yo esas
things about how great Juan Guarnizo is
cosas de qué grande Juan guarnizo
coming to Spain this week but he's not
viniendo esta semana a España pero no se
staying on Friday for the Eslan, a round of
queda el viernes para los eslan un
applause in
aplauso en
Mexico, in Mexico for whatever it was, he was
México en México por lo que fuera estuvo
there. The first one, a round of applause guys for
all El primero un aplauso chicos para
Juan
Juan
Guarnizo in Mexico for whatever it was, he was the
guarnizo en México por lo que fuera
first one, let's see, let's see, this was
estuvo el primer a ver a ver esto ha
because Ari was a presenter, it
sido porque Ari fue presentadora que me
seems very strong to me that Ari was the
parece muy fuerte que Ari fuera
presenter of the Iceland. But well, that
presentadora de los hland Pero bueno eso
will be a debate that uh that would be done at
ya será un debate que eh que se haría en
another time, okay
otro momento vale
[Music] let's
[Música]
see, I think that I think that about
m a ver yo creo que yo creo que lo de
Juan. It's a
Juan Es una
joke, he said that he's returning before the, I
broma lo dijo que se regresa antes de
mean, he said it, but I think he
los el o sea él lo ha dicho pero yo creo
's
que está
playing some kind of joke that he's not going to
jugando algún tipo de broma de que no va
go because there are no hotels, I don't know what, I do
a ir porque no hay hoteles no sé qué que
n't know how much it costs. But I think he's going to
no sé cuánto vale Pero yo creo que sí va
go, I mean, I would be very surprised if he didn't
a ir o sea me extrañaría mucho que no
go because apart from
fuera porque aparte
Ari, Juan is not in the best of
Ari Juan no están en el mejor de los
moments, they are interested in appearing in  these
momentos les interesa aparecer en este
types of events and
tipo de eventos y de
things are
cosas
worth it Juan already said that he knows they will
vale Juan ya dijo que sabe que lo
call him a hypocrite if he goes to Andorra but a
llamarán hipócrita si va a andorra pero
hypocrite why let's
hipócrita por
see if yes yes if it's a joke it's a silly joke
a ver si si si es una broma es una
okay if it's a joke it's a
vale si es una broma es una chorrada de
silly joke and I don't know why he does it okay But
broma y no sé por qué lo hace vale Pero
if it's
si es
true Well yes it seems a
verdad Pues sí que me parece un
little ugly
poco feucho
no I
no
mean he's been
o sea ha estado
in the Hland in Mexico his wife
en en los hland de México su mujer
working as a presenter who
trabajando de presentadora que
surely has a huge salary
seguramente tendría un sueldazo de la
they had a lot of prominence
[__] tuvieron ellos mucho protagonismo
plus they didn't act like that
además no hicieron como ese
tser it would be ugly the
tser estaría feucho la
truth so let's see if it's not a joke
verdad entonces a ver si no es una broma
by Juan and they're both pretending and they
de Juan y están fingiendo los dos y
're with punctures for this joke that we're
están con pinchados para esta broma que
going to see him next week okay
lo vamos a ver la semana que viene vale
Juan already has plans for those days I mean it's
Juan ya tiene planes para esos días o
confirmed
sea está confirmadísimo
what vaar IV hasn't written to me
qué vaar IV no me ha vuelto a escribir
anything again about coku he chickened out eh the
nada sobre coku se rajó eh el gigante
noble giant chickened
noble se
out Juan is in Spain for the
rajó Juan está en España por la final de
Queens final and today he was with esp who by the
la Queens y Hoy estuvo con esp que por
way his team has already been eliminated
cierto ya eliminaron a su equipo
[Music]
[Música]
m what do we do chat No it's just that these are
m qué hacemos chat No ya es que son
things that one  it's that nothing can be done
cosas que uno es que no se puede hacer
they scored a
nada han metido un gol de
golden goal a legal goal I mean it was a goal that they
oro un gol legal o sea sido un gol que
had to score and that's it
que tenían que meter y ya
and that's it but oh well look at the
está y ya está pero bueno Mira la
situation the points thing and and the whole
situación tema puntos y y toda la
situation that we're living through I think long
situación que estamos viviendo yo creo
live Sevilla
que viva Sevilla
eh a Go that had to score a Go that they had
eh un Go que tenía que meter un Go que
to
tenían que
score now I mean at least I have it
meter ya o sea yo al menos la tengo
normalized the players are fine too
normalizada las jugadoras tamb bien
we take it game by game and we'll
vivimos partido a partido y nos
focus on the next one we're not
centraremos en el siguiente ya no nos
going to think and to calculate if
vamos a pensar y para a calcular si
we're
estamos
mathematically we think game by
matemáticamente pensamos partido a
game and that's it and I think we put on a
partido y punto y creo que hemos dado un
tremendous show in this game they have been
espectáculo tremendo en este partido han
eliminated well anyway
sido eliminadas bueno de todas maneras
I imagine that they
yo me imagino que el billete de vuelta
will have the same return ticket eh
lo tendrá igual eh
maybe they lost or they won't have it
igual perdieran o no lo tendrán
scheduled okay for one date
programado vale para una fecha
but [ __ ] that Juan isn't going not this
pero [__] que que Juan no vaya no este
year there aren't a ton there are a few
año no hay un montón de hay unos cuantos
creators I don't know if a ton but
de creadores no sé si un montón pero
a few that aren't going Oh not this year Let's go
unos cuantos que no van Ay este año
Thank you Juan we love you
no Vamos allá Gracias Juan te queremos
But Spain is coming this week with
Pero por viene esta semana España con
all its [ __ ] but on Friday
toda su [__] pero el viernes no se
the slams are not staying each one does what they
quedan los slam a cada uno que haga lo
want
que le salga de la poll
well room for
bueno cabida de
Mini It's that  I don't want to talk and I don't want to
Mini Es que no quiero hablar y no quiero
talk and put my foot in it so that it's a
hablar y meter la pata para que sea una
joke and And yes, go to the
broma y Y sí que vaya ya a los
elan okay but for many things for
elan vale pero por muchas cosas por
many
muchas
things I would be very interested that not to
cosas Quedaría muy interesado que que no
support the eslan
apoyarse los eslan
man Because it's not that they have been
tío Porque que es que no es que han
part of the project in some
formado parte del proyecto de alguna
way, I mean, take the week that the
forma o sea toma la la semana que la
second edition there yes your wife of Oh I have
edición dos ahí sí tu mujer de Ay tengo
the exclusive sign Why if this
el cartel de exclusiva Por qué si esto
is not an exclusive
no es una exclusiva
eh there the the other week yes I mean the
eh ahí la la otra semana sí O sea la
other edition damn with the [ __ ] week the the
otra edición [__] con la [__] semana la
other edition
la otra edición
Yes your wife works even there you are also
Sí tu mujer trab incluso allí tú también
part of the
formáis parte del
project I don't know the truth I want to continue
proyecto no sé la verdad quiero seguir
thinking that it's a joke eh And Ari
pensando que sea una broma eh Y la Ari
is in Spain you know better than me
está en España tú lo sabes mejor que yo
Karime you're the one who sent me the
Karime que eres la que me has mandado la
info Well I think no it wouldn't look
info Pues creo que no
bad eh it would look bad if
no quedaría mal eh quedaría mal que no
things weren't presented as they are eh that
se presente las cosas como son eh que no
Javi is not going to go Enough already
va a ir Javi Basta ya
well take Javi auron and the salsería I
bueno toma Javi auron y la salsería te
appreciate it Jean I appreciate it
lo agradezco Jean te lo agradezco
very much and I send you a big kiss
muchísimo y te mando un beso muy fuerte
for Juan I understand that he's not going but
por Juan lo entiendo que no vaya pero
the others are not going to the
los demás no van a los hlan pero la
hlan but the evening Yeah I mean the whole group isn't going I mean isn't going Rivers isn't going well I understand Ari isn't going of course I mean isn't going Rivers isn't going Mariana I understand she's not going ama blis no Ari is hanging out with Rivers in the United States at
Ari anda con rivers en Estados Unidos en
the Super
la Super
Bowl I mean the elan are going
Bowl O sea a los elan van
there well we'll see
ahí bueno ya lo veremos la semana que
next week but there are many missing no that aren't going
viene pero faltan muchos no que no van
I think El Rubius is going in the end because he
creo que El Rubius al final s va porque
promised it to a follower and maybe he got it right
se lo prometió a un seguidor y por ahí
no maybe he got it
se la ha sacado no por ahí se la ha
right apart Well I think Rubius
huevos aparte Bueno pues creo que Rubius
and Gref have certain
y gref pues tienen ciertas
collaborations
colaboraciones
mm Jordi wil we forget that he's going
mm Jordi wil nos olvidamos de que vaya
No
No
yv I don't think he's going and me Juan will go No
yv creo que no va y yo Juan se irá No
man after last year he
hombre después de que el año pasado se
took 15 friends
llevó a 15 amigos
no Sprint either of course Sprint I understand
no Sprint tampoco claro Sprint entiendo
that neither
que tampoco
[ __ ] but delox is going Hey I could go Hey yes I yes I
hostias pero va el delox Oye podría ir
say I'll go there will be
yo Oye si yo si yo digo de ir habrá
room yes there won't be room no Hey I'm going not
hueco sí no habrá hueco no Oye voy no me
going to let me Gref
va a dejar el gref
no tomorrow the chefs win Javi if they win I'll
no mañana ganan los chef Javi si ganan
give you  10 bucks worth Jean I get your
te doy 10 pavos vale Jean te Pillo la
word and go and don't go I think so eh Let's
palabra y va y no va Yo creo que sí
see I would
eh A ver yo
go but it's just that I'm not into it I left a gap there
iría pero es que no me va dej ahí hueco
because no one goes and me Juan said he was too
hay porque no va nadie y yo Juan dijo
lazy don't [ __ ] with me and Juan said he's
pereza no me jodas y y Juan ha dicho que
not going because he's too
no va porque le da
lazy you must be fake Javi But why
pereza serás falsillas Javi Pero por qué
why would I be well it's
por qué voy a ser
not better for me to go and find out about
pues no es mejor que vaya y me entere de
the gossips there they're gossiping with
los cotillos allí est chismorreando con
one and another but what a fake I
uno y con otro pero que falsilla he
said that the eslan are nice I
dicho que los eslan están guapo a mí que
don't like him he's gref I don't give a damn about the slam I mean he's
no me cae bien es gref los slam me la
nice I
sudan o sea está guapo yo
would go see but but he wouldn't let me
iría a ver pero pero no me dejaría él
in obviously he wouldn't let me go
entrar evidentemente él no me dejaría ir
but yes it's true that there's a gap
pero sí que es verdad que hueco hay
eh I think he didn't like the news you
eh creo que no le gustó la noticia que
gave about grandma Oh it's true it's
diste de la abuela Ay es verdad es
true he probably didn't
verdad eso seguramente no le habrá
like that do you think he saw my
gustado creéis que la habrá visto mi
exclusive about grandma
exclusiva de la abuela
and Jo Juan said he's not going because greev wasn't
y Jo Juan dijo que no va porque greev no
going to give him like 20 tickets for his
le iba a dar como 20 entradas para sus
friends but how come he doesn't
amigos pero cómo que no se las
give them to him  but apart from the fakes, you're all
da pero aparte falsillas yos todos
whole, not everyone there, what do I care?
enteros no todos los que están allí qué
Go with Lorena and record with Delox, let's
más ve con Lorena y grabas con delox a
see. I see that I should go with
ver yo veo que debería ir con
Delox. He
delox
's there to veto. Of course, right
está el para vetar hombre claro es que
now there's a lack of people. Guys, I'm
ahora mismo haí falta gente chicos me
leaving. Okay, handsome. I'm leaving. If you go, they'll
voy vale guapísimos me voy si vas te
buy you. Javi. I'm priceless. I would
compran Javi No tengo precio les
betray you. After
traicionaría después de
selling myself. Guys, I'm
venderme chicos me
leaving tomorrow. See you later. Okay,
piro mañana nos vemos vale
handsome.
guapos
Bye.
chao